- ♪
音乐电
- MALE SINGER: ♪ MTV ♪
视音乐电
- [alarm bells ringing]
视音乐电视
- [horn blaring]
音乐电视
- [ringing continues]
- Come on! That boat's, like,
a light year away!
拜托! 那艘船离我们好像有一光年远！
- [boat horn blaring]
[船的喇叭声]
- At some point, I'm gonna start
taking this personally!
有时候我会觉得这是针对我个人！
You can't just ignore me,
Raymond! I'm not your wife!
你不能无视我，雷蒙德! 我不是你的妻子！
Asshole.
混蛋。
- [Little Richard singing
"Get Down With It"]
- [小理查德唱“ Get Down With It”]
♪ Well, all right ♪
好吧，好吧
♪ Well, all right, everybody ♪
好了，好了，各位
- [bicycle bell ringing]
[自行车铃响]
- [people cheering]
[人们欢呼]
- ♪ Let your hair down ♪
放下你的头发
- Aren't you supposed
to get somebody
你不是应该找个人
to ride that with you?
和你一起骑马吗？
- ♪ If you got on a wig like
some people think I got on ♪
如果你戴上假发，就像有些人认为我戴上的那样
♪ And this is my own
beautiful hair, ♪
这是我自己美丽的头发
♪ What to do with it, fellas ♪
怎么办，伙计们
- CROWD: Take it off!
脱下来！
- ♪ I said and get
down on with it ♪
我说了，继续唱下去
♪ Do the jazz ♪
来点爵士乐吧
♪ Come on, baby ♪
来吧，宝贝
♪ Wanna watch everybody work ♪
我要看着每个人工作
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪噢，耶♪
♪ Come on, baby, yeah ♪
来吧，宝贝，耶
♪ Wanna see everybody
do the jerk ♪
我要看到每个人都这么跳
♪ Oh, come on, baby ♪
来吧，宝贝
♪ It's been a long, long time ♪
已经很久很久了
♪ I said come on, baby ♪
我说来吧，宝贝
♪ Wanna watch everybody
move around, yeah, yeah ♪
要看每个人移动，是的，是的
♪ I said, come on, baby ♪
我说，来吧，宝贝
♪ I'm gonna watch
everybody move around ♪
我要看着每个人移动
♪ Want everybody in the house
to raise both your hands ♪
♪希望屋子里的每个人都举起双手♪
♪ Everybody raise
both your hands ♪
大家举起双手
♪ I said stomp your
feet, everybody ♪
我让你们跺脚，大家
♪
♪ Stomp your feet ♪
跺跺你的脚
♪ Now let's get with
my little beat ♪
现在开始我的小节拍吧
♪ Everybody stomp
your feet, oh ♪
大家跺跺脚，哦
♪ Now get this
Little Richard's beat ♪
现在来听听小理查德的节奏
♪ Oh, one more time ♪
哦，再来一次
♪ I'm singin' one more time ♪
我再唱一次
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, woo ♪
♪耶，耶，耶，耶，耶，耶，耶，喔
♪ My, my, my, my, hey, yeah ♪
我的，我的，我的，嘿，耶
♪ Singin' one more time ♪
∮再唱一次∮
♪ I'm dancin' one more time ♪
我再跳一次舞
♪ Oh, yes, all right ♪
哦，是的，好吧
♪ I'm singin' it's all right ♪
我在唱歌，一切都很好
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪耶，耶，耶，耶，耶♪
♪ My, my, my, my, hey ♪
我，我，我，我，嘿
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪耶，耶，耶，耶，耶♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my ♪
我，我，我，我，我
♪ Oh, it's all right ♪
哦，没关系
♪ I'm singin' it's all right ♪
我在唱歌，一切都很好
♪ Woo ♪
♪呜♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪耶，耶，耶♪
♪ My, my, my, my ♪
我的，我的，我的
♪♪
♪
- [crowd applause]
[人群鼓掌]
- BOY: Just these.
就这些。
Oh!
哦! 这些
These too.
也是。
- Those don't always
work, you know.
你知道，那些东西并不总是管用的。
- Okay.
好吧。
- GIRL: Oh, babe, but
I like bubble gum.
宝贝，我喜欢泡泡糖。
- "But I like bubble gum."
-”但我喜欢泡泡糖”
The condoms.
Talking about the condoms.
-安全套说到安全套。
First, you two get handsy in
the back of his mom's Jetta.
首先，你们俩在他妈妈的捷达后座上亲热。
You say some cheesy line
about how hot she is.
你说了一些关于她有多性感的俗套话。
She massages her nipples.
她按摩她的乳头。
And then after warming
up his stick shift with
然后在用卷心菜贴唇
the Cabbage Patch lip gloss,
膏热身变速杆之后,
you would gently
slip on a Trojan,
你会轻轻滑上特洛伊木马,
the mightiest of
soldiers, and you think,
最强大的士兵，你认为,
"Great, now I'm not
gonna get pregnant."
“太好了，现在我不会怀孕了。”但
But you're wrong,
Hannah Montana.
是你错了，汉娜・蒙塔娜。
Maybe there's no baby, but
sure enough, the condom rips,
也许没有孩子，但是很明显，避孕套破了,
and you get chlamydia--
你会得衣原体感染这是上帝对性
God's punishment for
the sexually-active.
行为活跃的人的惩罚。
You gotta get a shot from
your judgmental pediatrician
你应该去看看你那个还戴着米
who still wears
Mickey Mouse ties.
老鼠领带的儿科医生。
You better hope
that's all you get,
你最好希望你只能得到这些,
because, worse-case scenario,
you're pregnant and dead,
因为更糟糕的情况是你怀孕了而且死了,
all because he stuck his
dick in some SAT tutor
都是因为他在塞给你之前把老二塞给了某个
before he shoved it in you.
SAT 辅导老师。
- [gasps]
一共七块五。
- That's gonna be $7.50.
- ♪
♪
- You look like shit.
你看起来糟透了。
- Say that about
my grandson again,
你再这么说我孙子,
and you'll pay for it later.
你以后会付出代价的。
- Oh, yeah? Well, you look
like shit. Come here.
是吗? 你看起来糟透了过来。
- I am begging
you guys to stop.
我求你们了。
- Oh!
- 哦!-还
- Also, Janine is relentless.
有 Janine 冷酷无情。
- Put that damn
duck in the drawer
- 把那该死的鸭
with the rest of 'em, will you?
子和其他东西一起放到抽
Okay?
屉里，
- CALEB: Yeah.
好吗?-好的。
- Your graduation is tomorrow.
你明天就毕业了。
- Oh my god, it is?
- VALERIE: Yeah,
- 哦，我的上帝，是吗?-是的,
and I think that it'd be
very nice if you went.
我觉得如果你能去。
- Yeah, but then I'd miss
the "Golden Girls" marathon.
是啊但那样我就错过”黄金女郎”马拉松了。
- Has it ever occurred to you
that we might want to go
你有没有想过我们可能会去庆祝
and celebrate your
accomplishments,
你的成就,
however mediocre they might be?
不管他们有多平庸
- No one's stopping you, Benny.
Enjoy it.
?-没人阻止你，班尼。好好享受吧。
- And try
and get some sleep!
- 试着睡会儿吧
You really do look like shit.
! 你看起来真的很糟糕。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
- ♪
- [quiet sobbing]
[安静的哭泣声]
- WOMAN: Caleb Cohn?
- Yeah.
- Caleb Cohn?-是的。
- [door creaking]
早上好。
- DR. DIAZ: Good morning.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Cohn.
很高兴见到你，科恩先生。
I'm Dr. Diaz.
So, what are we doing today?
我是迪亚兹医生。那么，我们今天做什么
Uh, an STD check?
? 呃，性病检查?-是的，
- Yeah, that's
kind of why I'm here.
这就是我来这里的原因。
I just wanna, like,
test the shit out of me
我只是想测试一下自己，
so all this can be over.
这样一切就都结束了。
The condom broke.
避孕套破了。
Yeah, apparently it was expired
like a fucking avocado.
是的，很明显它像他妈的鳄梨一样过期了。
- When did that happen?
- Last Thursday night.
- 什么时候的事?-上周四晚上。
I went to this new biker
bar called The Ram Rod.
我去了一家新开的摩托车手酒吧，叫做 The Ram Rod。
Met this Slavic guy
认识了这个斯拉
who knew every single Best
Actress winner since 1962,
夫人他认识1962年以来的所有最佳女主角得主,
so I had sex with him.
所以我就和他上床了。
- Okay. [chuckling]
- 好吧
- He sent me a
message last night.
-他昨晚给我发了条短信。
"Ahoj, Caleb.
“喂，卡莱布。
"I tested HIV-positive Monday.
“我星期一检测出艾滋病毒呈阳性。
"Swear I not know.
“我发誓我不知道。
"I'm sure you make joke on
this I no understand, bye.
“我知道你在开玩笑，我不明白，再见。
Zander."
Zander”
- Well, you've come
to the right place.
-你来对地方了。
We'll test you for all STDs and
have your HIV baseline today.
今天我们将为你做所有性传播疾病的检测，并且给你做 HIV 基线测试。
Then you can make
appointments to the front desk
然后你可以在前台预约
to come back for
your HIV re-checks.
时间回来做 HIV 复查。
- No, no need to re-check.
不，不需要重新检查。
I am officially
celibate until death.
我是正式的独身主义者直到死。
- Right.
对。
Look, today's test
won't determine whether
听着，今天的测试不能确
you contracted the virus
from this exposure.
定你是否因为这次接触而感染了病毒。
The test looks for
HIV antibodies,
检测是为了寻找 HIV 抗体,
and they take time to develop.
它们需要时间来发展。
In the meantime,
与此同时,
I run a support
group twice a week.
我每周组织两次互助小组。
We'd be happy to have you.
我们很高兴你能来。
- Yeah, but, like, I
don't even know if I have it.
是啊但我都不知道自己有没有。
- Well, it's not only
for people who are positive.
不仅仅是对那些乐观的人。
This is sort of a any queer
person who wants to talk
这是那种想聊天吃免费饼干
and eat free cookies
kind of group,
的同性恋群体,
so it's for people in
your position, too.
所以对于你这样的人来说也是如此。
- Okay, and, um,
typically how long
像我这样的人
does somebody in my
position have to wait
要等
to know if they
have it for sure?
多久才
- ♪
能确定？- ♪
- [Le Tigre singing
"Deceptacon"]
- [ Le Tigre 演唱“霸天虎”]
♪ Who took the bomp ♪
谁拿走了炸弹
♪
♪ Every day and night ♪
每一天每一夜
♪ Wanna disco,
wanna see me disco ♪
要跳迪斯科，要看我跳迪斯科
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
一，二，三，四
♪ You got you been asking for ♪
你得到了你一直要求的东西
♪ You're so policy-free
and your fantasy wheels ♪
你是如此的自由和你的幻想轮子
♪ And everything you feel
is alright ♪
你感觉到的一切都很好
♪ Alright,
alright, alright ♪
好了，好了，好了
♪ Who took the bomp from
the bompalompalomp ♪
谁从炸弹手里抢走了炸弹
♪ Who too the ram from
the ramalamdingdong ♪
歌声中的公羊也是谁
- DARA: 'Bout time, bitch.
时间到了，婊子。
- I'm sorry.
What'd I miss?
- 对不起，我错过什么了?
- Fuck if I know.
-我怎么知道。
Fell asleep when Chloe
dedicated her diploma
当克洛伊把她的毕业证书献给耶
to Jesus and Jeb Bush.
稣和杰布 · 布什时，她睡着了。
- Gross.
- 真恶心。
- MAN: Kristy Quinlon.
- [crowd applauding]
克里斯蒂 · 昆伦。他们
- CALEB: Did they
make it to the Vs?
打到 v 了吗？谁
- Who cares if Dom
has walked yet? It's over.
在乎 Dom 走了没有？结束了。
- All I ever wanted was
a boy to dry hump me
我曾经只想要一个男孩坐在他爸爸的
in the back of his dad's Prius,
and now that dream is dead.
普锐斯后座上干我，现在这个梦想破灭了。
- You're so dramatic.
- I'm in mourning.
- 你太戏剧化了-我在服丧。
- You're always
mourning something.
你总是在哀悼什么。
- First of all, rude.
首先，很粗鲁。
Second of all, it's different.
其次，这是不同的。
It's Dom.
是多姆。
- MAN: Sarah Stein.
莎拉・斯坦。
- DARA: Made these for you.
这是为你做的。
- Oh, so Suzanne
didn't want them?
- 哦那 Suzanne 不想吃
- I don't know why she
keeps rejecting my quiche.
了?-我不知道她为什么一直不吃我的乳蛋饼。
- You know, it could be
because she's our boss?
- 有可能是因为她是我们的老
- Didn't stop her from
eating it last summer.
板?-去年夏天她就吃了。
[laughing]
Look, I know this is hard,
我知道这很难接受,
but you gotta look
at the upside.
但你得看看好的一面。
Now you get to sit on a
new face, a better face.
现在你可以坐在一张新面孔上，一张更好的面孔。
- MAN: Andy Terasaki.
Andy Terasaki.
- Maybe I already did.
- Of course you already did!
- 也许我已经做了-你当然已经做了! 那家伙是谁?
Who's the guy?
-他的名字
- His name was Zander.
是 Zander。
He didn't speak a
word of English,
他一句英语都不会说,
he was part Slav,
part, like, horse.
他有一半斯拉夫血统一半马血统。
- Was?
- 以前?-是的，
- Yeah, he to fly back to
Belgrade a couple days ago.
他几天前要飞回贝尔格莱德。
He sent me a message.
他给我发了条信息。
- MAN: Dom Valdez.
唐 · 瓦尔德斯。
- [camera shutter clicking]
莎拉
[camera shutter clicking]
· 瓦
- MAN: Sarah Valdez.
尔迪兹。
- Caleb.
卡莱布。
You're gonna be okay.
你会没事的。
- Am I?
- 是吗
- People live with
this shit forever now.
?-现在人们永远背负着这个鬼东西。
- Kinda feel like I live
with enough shit already.
我觉得我已经够倒霉的了。
- Did you tell your grandma?
你告诉你奶奶了吗？
- Why scare a woman who's
already lost her only son
为什么要吓唬一个已经失去独子的女人
when I can just, like, quietly
die alone on the inside?
而我却可以悄悄地死在里面？
- MAN: And now once again, class
valedictorian Chloe Smith.
男: 现在再一次，毕业生代表克洛伊史密斯。
- ♪
祝贺201
- CHLOE: Congrats,
class of 2011.
We did it!
我们成功了！
- [bell ringing]
嘿
- Hey.
。
So I spent the last couple of
days looking at...AIDS stuff.
所以我花了几天时间研究... 艾滋病的东西。
- Jesus, fuck, Dara!
- 天啊，操，达拉!-
- Did your doctor
tell you about PEP?
你的医生告诉你 PEP 的
- He did not.
事了吗?-他没有。
- Well, it's this thing
that you take right after
这是一种在你被感染后
you've been exposed, and it
can help get rid of AIDS.
立即服用的药物它可以帮助你摆脱艾滋病。
- Okay, but this says
you can only take it
好吧但这上面说你只能在
up to three days
after having sex.
做爱后三天内服用。
It's been, like, a week.
- Isn't it work asking about?
已经一个星期了-不是工作上的事吗？
- [phone ringing]
骄傲中心。
- MAN: Pride Center.
- Yeah, hi, I'm
looking for Dr. Diaz.
你好我找迪亚兹医生。
- MAN: Oh, he's not
available right now.
他现在没空。
- Please, it's a super-quick
life-or-death question.
拜托这是个生死攸关的问题。
- MAN: If this is a medical
emergency,
如果这是紧急医疗事故,
please hang up and dial 911.
请挂断然后拨911。
- I can't, they
hate me over there.
不行他们讨厌我。
- MAN: He's upstairs
at his group meeting
- 他在楼上开
if you want to come by.
- [phone beeps]
小组会议，如果你想来的话。
- I gotta leave early.
- Okay.
我得早点走。好吧。
- [bell ringing]
- Uhhh, ah.
呃，啊。
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我迟到了。
I got stuck
with the principal!
我被校长缠住了!
Riley won't stop drawing
boobs on his homework.
莱利一直在家庭作业上画胸部。
He's obsessed.
他被迷住了。
I don't know where
he gets this from.
我不知道他从哪儿学来的。
- [scoffs]
卡莱布，你能
- Caleb, can you help me
replace the slushee machine?
帮我换一下冰淇淋
It's so heavy.
机吗? 太重了。
- I can do it.
我可以的。
I've been lifting.
我一直在举重。
- [chuckling] Okay.
好吧。
- Go! Go, you have to!
- 走! 走，
- ♪
你必须走!-莱顿
- [indistinct chatter]
[模糊的谈话声]
- CALEB: Hi.
- You came.
- 嗨-你来了。
- What is PEP?
- 什么是
And how can I get on
it, like, right now?
PEP？我现在怎么上去
- Why don't we grab a coffee?
？我们去喝杯咖啡怎么
It's only effective within
three days of exposure.
样？只有在暴露三天内才有效。
- And why did you not
tell me about that before?
你之前为什么不告诉我？因为
- Because I didn't want to
tell you about something
我不想告诉你一些你用
you couldn't use.
不上的东西。
- It's been, like, a week.
- Caleb.
- 好像有一周了吧-Caleb。
- Maybe it'll still work.
Can we just, like--
- 也许还能用我们能不
Can we just, like, try, please?
能...-我们能不能试试？
- Listen, I want you to
stay for group tonight.
听着，我要你今晚留下来参加小组讨论。
You haven't lived
until you've tried
如果你没有尝过 Lis
one of Lisha's donuts,
so do yourself a favor.
ha 做的甜甜圈，你就没有活过，所以帮自己一个忙吧。
Oh, and we go to karaoke after.
然后我们去唱卡拉 ok。
All right, guys,
let's bring it in.
好了，伙计们，开始吧。
Welcome to "The Young
and The Sexless."
欢迎收看”年轻人与性冷淡
Jim, you're up.
”吉姆，该你了。
- JIM: [laughing]
嗨，我是吉姆，
Hi, I'm Jim, and I'm
married to Dr. Oz.
我嫁给了奥兹医生。
Well, I've been positive--
嗯，我一直很肯定
[muffled voice]
——[低沉的声音]
- I saw that.
我看到了。
- Would you like a prize?
- 你想要奖品吗
- Not if it's one
of those donuts.
?-如果是甜甜圈就不要了。
- JIM: --their lives and their
sex lives
- JIM: -- 他们的生活和
aren't over after diagnosis.
性生活在确诊后还没有结束。
Anywho,
once we found out,
不管怎样一旦我们发现,
we did all the right things
我们做了所有正确的事
to ensure that
Adrian was protected.
来确保艾德里安受到保护。
Undetectable means
untransmittable.
不可检测的意思是不能传送的。
Both, uh, true fact
既是事实又是我即
and the title of
my upcoming memoir.
将出版的回忆录的标题。
- [laughing]
- 你呢?
- How about you?
想分享一
You care to share?
下吗?-好吧我
- Okay, um, well, I'm Caleb.
叫 Caleb。
I, um--I'm here
because a condom broke.
我来是因为避孕套破了。
The guy had HIV, and now
I'm waiting to find out
那家伙有艾滋病，
if I do, too. Oldest story in--
现在我正等着看我是否也有。
- [bag popping]
最古老的故事——-[袋子爆开
- CALEB: --book or something.
]-迦勒: ——书还是什么的。
Uh, I'm supposed to
go to Parsons,
我要去帕森斯学院,
but their tuition
costs as much as
但他们的学费相当于一
a small chain of
islands, so, we'll see.
个小岛链的费用，所以，我们拭目以待。
Oh, and I work at the
mini-mart on 72nd,
我在72街的小超市工作,
so, slushee
discounts all around.
那么，斯鲁希全面打折。
- That's great.
太好了。
Thank you, Caleb.
谢谢你 Caleb。
And Estha?
还有 Estha？
- Hi. Um, my name's Estha,
- 嗨-我叫 Estha,
and, uh, I'm also waiting.
我也在等。
- ♪
- ♪ All through the night ♪
整个夜晚
♪ Stray cat is crying ♪
“流浪猫在哭泣”
♪ So stray cat sings back ♪
于是流浪猫唱回来
♪ All through the night ♪
整个夜晚
♪ They have forgotten
what by day they lack ♪
他们已经忘记了白天他们缺少什么
♪ Under those white
street lamps ♪
在那些白色的街灯下
♪ There is a little chance ♪
有一点机会
- Hey, it's Estha, right?
你是 Estha 对吧？
I brought you a karaoke book.
我给你带了本卡拉 ok 书。
I don't know if you
already have one,
我不知道你是不是已经有了,
but I thought you might need
one if you wanted to sing?
但我想如果你想唱歌的话可能需要一个?
- I don't do
karaoke, I'm tone-deaf.
-我不唱卡拉 ok，我是音盲。
- If only that stopped
everyone, right?
要是这能阻止所有人
- ♪ And once we start,
the meter clicks ♪
就好了，对吧？一旦我们开始，节拍就响了
♪ And it goes running ♪
♪它就开始跑了♪也许你
- Maybe you should
sing something.
应该唱点什么。
- Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
No, the last time I did karaoke,
不上次我唱卡拉 ok,
I totally butchered my
favorite Bowie song,
我把我最喜欢的鲍伊的歌弄得一团糟,
and I still feel the shame.
我仍然感到羞耻。
- Who's that?
- 那是
- Bowie.
谁?-鲍伊。
Like, David Bowie.
Like, Ziggy Stardust.
比如，大卫 · 鲍伊，瑞格 · 星尘。
Kinda looks like a man,
kinda looks like an alien,
有点像男人有点像外星人,
kinda looks like something
看起来像是你在黑
you'd want to avoid
in a dark basement.
暗的地下室里，最不想看到的东西。
- Nope.
没有。
- Do you live under
a rock or something?
- 你是住在石头下面还是什么?-不，
- No, I'm from India.
我来自印度。
- Plenty of rocks in India.
印度有很多岩石。
- Sorry?
什么？好吧
- Okay, well, what
would you sing
如果你要唱什么
if you had to sing something?
你会唱什么
- Out of American music?
？没有美国
- Sure.
音乐了？当然。
- Probably Taylor Swift.
可能是泰勒 · 斯威夫特。
- [chuckling]
天啊，你是
Oh my god, you're serious.
认真的。
- What? Sometimes I feel like
she steals my journal
- 什么?-有时候我觉得她
and writes about my life.
偷了我的日记还写了我的生活。
- Is her next crossover
hit gonna be called,
她的下一部跨界作品会叫,
"This Is What I Get
For Riding Bareback?"
“这就是我骑无
- ♪
鞍马得到的?”-让我们
- Let's hope not.
希望不是。
[laughing]
直到它结束♪没
- JIM: ♪ Until it ends ♪
有结束♪-
♪ There is no end ♪♪
迦勒: 很高兴见
- CALEB: It was
cool to meet you.
到你。
- ESTHA: It's good
to meet you too.
我也很高兴见到你。
- Did you, um--did
you drive here?
- 你是开车来的吗?-不是我
- No, I, uh, took the bus.
是坐公车来的。
I have to, uh, ask my
parents' permission
我必须得到我父母的允
to use their car
specifically for my friends.
许才能专门为我的朋友们开车。
- Yeah, yeah, I haven't
told my grandma either.
我也没告诉我奶奶。
- It's just easier since
they don't know about
因为他们
the whole gay thing.
不知道同性恋的事。
- Do you want a ride?
你想骑车吗? 我
I have a tandem bike.
有一辆双人自行车。
That means two people can--
这意味着两个人可
- I know what a tandem bike is.
以 ---我知道什么是双人自行车。
- You didn't know Bowie, so,
like, I didn't want to assume.
你不认识 Bowie 所以我不想假设。
- I, uh--I live a
couple miles away.
我住在几英里外。
- That's okay.
Uh, you can help me pedal.
没关系你可以帮我踩踏板。
- Okay.
好吧。
- Cool. Um, I parked
in this creepy side alley.
- 酷-我把车停在一个诡异的小巷里。
Don't worry,
I'm not gonna murder you.
别担心，我不会杀你的。
- You say very strange things.
你说了很奇怪的话。
- I get that a lot.
经常有人这么说。
- ♪
- How's it going back there?
- 后面怎么样了
- I'm afraid you're gonna crash.
?-恐怕你要撞车了。
- It's my dad's bike.
I can ride with my eyes closed.
这是我爸的自行车我闭着眼睛也能骑。
- Yeah, I really
rather you didn't.
是啊，我真的希望你不要。
- Noted.
- 知道了。
So when did you start
going to those meetings?
你什么时候开始参加那些会议的?-
- About three weeks ago.
大概三个星期前。
It's nice to talk
to people, so--
和人交谈是件好事，所以小心
Watch out for the pothole.
路上的坑洞。
- Sure.
当然。
Well, how'd you get into this
mess in the first place?
你是怎么卷进来的？去
- Last year my parents
started introducing me
年我父母开始把我介绍给
to their friends' daughters,
and every time I say no,
他们朋友的女儿每次我拒绝,
there'd be another one waiting.
还会有另一个人在等你。
- Assembly line dating?
- 流水线约会
Yeah, my mom did the
exact same thing.
?-是啊我妈也是这么干的。
- Is she conservative?
- 她保守吗?-
- Oh, she's Jewish.
她是犹太人。
Orthodox Jewish.
东正教犹太教徒。
Yeah, mentally and emotionally,
she's stuck in a shtetl in 1805.
是的，精神上和情感上，她被困在1805年的一个小镇里。
- ESTHA: You can stop here.
你可以在这里停车。
- [bike brakes creaking]
这就是你？没关系。你的
- So this is you, huh?
草坪很漂亮。
It's cool. You got a great lawn.
Says a lot about a person.
说明了很多关于一个人的事情。
Hmm, look at those
really nice bushes.
看看这些漂亮的灌木。
Perfectly trimmed, A-plus.
修剪得很好 a + 。
- Actually, I live
down the street,
事实上我住在街尾,
but I'll just walk.
但我还是走路吧。
- Do I give off, like,
我是不是散发出,
a serial killer
vibe or something?
连环杀手的气场还是什么？没有
- No, but my dad stays up late,
and I didn't want him seeing
但我爸爸很晚才睡我不想让他看见一个
a white boy drop me off
on a gay two-man bike.
白人男孩把我扔在一辆同性恋双人自行车上。
Might raise some questions.
可能会引起一些问题。
- Got it.
知道了。
- You seem nervous.
你看起来很紧张。
- No, I get, uh,
不我明白,
a little too talkative
around guys sometimes.
有时候在男人面前太多嘴了。
It's, like, I ask
a lot of questions.
我问了很多问题。
It's the thing that I do
that I might be working on.
这是我做的事情，我可能正在努力。
- I meant about
what's happening.
我是说发生了什么事。
The waiting.
等待。
- Um, yeah.
是的。
Yeah, sleeping's hard.
是啊，睡觉很困难。
That was very embarrassing,
by the way, when I implied that
顺便说一句，当我暗示你是个男人，我在你身边会感到
I get nervous around
you for being a guy.
紧张的时候，我觉得非常尴尬。
- If you can't sleep,
you can call me.
如果你睡不着，可以打电话给我。
Sometimes I can't sleep either,
有时候我也睡不着,
and, uh, don't really have
anybody to talk to.
没有人可以倾诉。
- ♪
- Are you writing your
number on a Subway coupon?
你把你的号码写在赛百味的优惠券上了吗？
You can type it in my phone.
你可以把它输入我的手机。
- ♪
- Are you going to
the next meeting?
- 你要去参
- Shh.
加下次会议吗?-嘘。
- [whispers]
Should I take that as a yes?
我应该把这当作是同意吗？
- [bell ringing]
[铃声]
- WOMAN: This is
the true story--
这是个真实的故事
- MAN: True story--
男人: 真实的故事
- WOMAN: Of seven strangers--
七个陌生人
- [man laughing]
[男人的笑声]
- MAN: Picked to
live in a house--
男人: 被选中住在一所房子里
- WOMAN: And have
their lives taped--
把他们的生活录下来
- MAN: Oh, Lucy, I'm home.
露西，我回来了。
- MAN: To find
out what happens--
- 为了找出发生了
- MAN: When people
stop being polite--
什么...-当人们不再彬彬有礼的时候...
- MAN: And start getting real.
-开始变得真实起来。
- MAN: "The Real World:
San Francisco."
《真实世界: 旧金山》佩德罗:
- PEDRO: I used to
go around to schools
我以前经常去
and I speak about HIV and AIDS.
学校，谈论艾滋病毒和艾滋病。
I'm HIV-positive.
我是 hiv 阳性。
- CORY: When Pedro told
me he was HIV-positive,
- CORY: 当 Pedro 告诉我他是 hiv 阳性时,
it was just, like,
"No, not him."
就像是”不不是他”我喜
I like this guy,
欢这家伙,
and I don't want him
to have to suffer.
我不想让他受苦。
- [phone chiming]
我在火车上
- CORY: I had an incredible time
talking to him on the train.
和他聊得很开心。
- PEDRO: Have you, uh,
been in a relationship?
你有没有谈过恋爱？- CORY: 我
- CORY: The longest relationship
I ever had is a year and a half.
有过的最长的恋爱关系是一年半。
- ♪
- 莱克: 我不
- CORY: And, I don't know.
I don't think I've ever...
知道，我从来没有..。
I don't really think
I've ever been in love.
我觉得我从来没有恋爱过。
- PEDRO: I get very
twisted, and, uh...
我变得非常扭曲。
- ♪
- 你在那
- CORY: What did you do
down there?
里做
What did you do for a living?
什么?
- ♪
你以什么为生?-超人
- PEDRO: --I'm still pretty
uncertain about, you know,
- 佩德罗:-我还是不确定，你知道,
meeting five people,
见了五个人,
and I don't know how they
going to feel about me
我不知道他们对我
being HIV-positive.
hiv 阳性会有什么感觉。
- [phone ringing]
看看你的手机，
- PHONE: Look at
your phone, bitch!
婊子
- [phone ringing]
！看看你的
- PHONE: Look at
your phone, bitch!
手机，
- [phone ringing]
婊子！看看你
- PHONE: Look at
your phone, bitch!
的手机，婊子！
- [phone chiming]
[电话铃声]
- MAN: Hey, it's the Pride
Center calling for Caleb Cohn.
男: 嘿，这里是荣誉中心，找 Caleb Cohn。
Dr. Diaz would like you to
stop by the clinic today.
迪亚兹医生希望你今天能去趟诊所。
Okay, thanks.
好的，谢谢。
- VALERIE: Caleb,
Dara's waiting for you!
- 卡莱布，达拉在等你!
- Oh, the Orion Condominium.
-哦，猎户座公寓。
Hmm, it's got a kosher
deli in the lobby.
嗯，大厅里有一家犹太熟食店。
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
- BENNY: But 25% off on
Thursdays for the residents.
- 本尼: 但是住院医生在星期四可以打八五折。
- And you want me to turn
in my home for a coupon?
- 你想让我去我家拿优惠券?-
- I would. Their noodle kugel
is next level.
我会的他们的面条布丁可是高级货。
The food here is good, too.
这里的食物也不错。
- BENNY: See? There he is!
Hey, tell me something.
- 看到了吗? 他在那儿!-嘿，告诉我。
Which one would you choose
你会选择哪一个让
for your grandmother
to live in with me?
你的祖母和我住在一起?-嗯
- Um--
- Don't distract him.
---别让他分心。
He's got enough on his mind
without worrying about
他已经够烦心的了，不用担心我
what nursing home
we should die in.
们会死在什么疗养院。
- Well, technically,
it's not a nursing home.
严格来说这不是疗养院。
It's a luxury condominium.
这是一套豪华公寓。
I promise I'll stop talking now.
我保证我现在不说话了。
- Okay, as
lovely as this has been,
虽然这里很漂亮,
um, we should go.
我们该走了。
- You should have some
coffee before you leave
你走之前应该喝点咖啡
because you look exhausted.
因为你看起来很累。
- These compliments so early.
Thank you.
- 这么早就表扬我了-谢谢。
- Thanks for the fish!
- 谢谢你的鱼！你觉
- Does he seem different to you?
得他有什么不同吗？他什么
- When does he not
seem different?
时候看起来没什么不
- ♪
同？我们上班要
- We're gonna be late for work.
- Oh, I'm not going to work.
迟到了。我不去上班了。
- What?
- Yeah.
- 什么?-是啊。
I am truly devastated to report
告诉大家我必须回到诊所
that I have to go
back to the clinic.
，我真的感到非常震惊。
- Again? Why?
- 又来了? 为什
- I don't know, so, naturally,
I'm assuming the worst.
么?-我不知道所以很自然地我就做了最坏的打算。
- All right, well,
好吧,
I guess I'll do
inventory by myself then.
我想我会自己做清单。
- CALEB: You're the messiah!
Owe you forever, love you, bye!
- 迦勒: 你是
- ♪
弥赛亚! 永远欠你，爱你，再见!-♪
- [knocking on door]
我会死吗？你有自杀
- Am I gonna die?
的计划
- Do you have any
plans to kill yourself?
吗？现在
- Not at the moment.
没有。
- DR. DIAZ: Then
you're not gonna die.
那你就不会死。
I will not let the anal
gonorrhea take you down.
我不会让肛门淋病带你下来。
- The fuck? Is that worse
than normal gonorrhea?
- 搞什么? 比正常的淋病还严重吗?-
- No, it's
just on the anus.
不只是肛门感染。
- You mean my butt?
- I'm a doctor, I mean anus.
- 你是说我的屁股?-我是个医生，我是说肛门。
- Okay, but I don't
have any symptoms.
好吧但我没有任何症状。
- Any soreness?
- 有酸痛吗?-我
- I guess, but
I just thought was from,
想是的但我以为是,
like, getting railed.
比如，被人批评。
- We'll take care of
the infection today.
我们今天会处理感染的。
But you should know that
the presence of gonorrhea
但你应该知道，淋病的
can help the contraction of HIV.
存在可以帮助收缩的艾滋病毒。
Are you allergic to any
medications, like penicillin?
你对什么药物过敏吗，比如青霉素?-
- I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
- DR. DIAZ: All right.
好吧。
Now, hop off the
table and bend over.
现在，跳下桌子，弯下腰。
- Story of my life.
我的人生故事。
So this should take care of it?
那么这个应该可以了?-
- Yep, penicillin is great.
是的，青霉素很好。
Alexander Fleming
discovered it in the '20s.
亚历山大·弗莱明在20世纪20年代发现了它。
- Good for her.
对她有好处。
- DR. DIAZ: He left his lab
a mess over the weekend.
他周末把实验室弄得一团糟。
When he got back, a weird fungus
had grown in a petri dish.
当他回来的时候，一种奇怪的真菌在培养皿中生长。
From that fungus,
we have penicillin.
从那种真菌中，我们发现了青霉素。
- Sounds disgusting.
听起来很恶心。
- Yeah,
but it's amazing
是啊，但是在生活变得一团
what you can discover
after life gets fucked up.
糟之后，你会发现很多东西。
- ♪
♪
- [bell ringing]
- ♪
- Dara?
达拉
- Are you out back?
你在后面吗？
- ♪
- You will not believe
the size of the--
- 你不会相信的大小-
- [Suzanne screaming]
- [苏珊娜尖叫]
- [Dara screaming]
- [screaming]
- [ Dara 尖叫]-[尖叫]
- SUZANNE: Pull up your pants!
- DARA: I'm trying!
- 拉上裤子!-我正在拉！
- SUZANNE: Try harder!
- DARA: I'm trying harder!
- 再努力点!-我正在努力！
Stop yelling at me!
别对我大喊大叫！
- ♪
- Hi. Do you wanna know the
craziest thing about doors?
- 嗨，你想知道门最疯狂的地方是什么吗?
You can lock them.
你可以锁门。
- Fuck, man, she's so mad.
妈的，伙计，她真是疯了。
If anyone asks, you
didn't see anything.
如果有人问起，就说你什么都没看见。
- I am literally trying to unsee
that as we speak.
我说话这会儿正在努力忘记这一点。
I thought she didn't
want to eat your quiche.
我以为她不想吃你的乳蛋饼。
- Oh, remember when
I covered for you?
还记得我帮你打掩护吗? 我
We got to talking,
and things started to happen,
们聊了聊然后事情就开始了,
and it was like--
就像...-我为自己
- It is bad enough that I'm
responsible for my own mistakes.
的错误负责已经够糟糕的了。
Do not make me responsible
for yours, too.
不要让我也为你的行为负责。
- Caleb?
凯勒布。
Uh...
- You're not gonna say anything.
你什么都不会说的。
You saw nothing.
你什么都没看见。
No, promise me.
不，答应我。
Caleb, say it!
Caleb，
Say it!
Promise me!
说啊! 说
- ♪
啊! 答应我!
- You rang?
-你按铃
- Sit.
了?-坐下。
Um, look, I'm having
such a shitty week, okay?
我这周过得糟透了好吗? Henry
Henry still hasn't found a job,
还没找到工作,
I'm doing double duty with
the fucking kids at home.
我在家里还要照顾孩子。
My dog got scabies
again at the dog park.
我的狗在狗公园又得了疥疮。
My mother-in-law is visiting.
我婆婆来看我了。
I--
我真的很
I'm really not happy.
不开心。
- You looked pretty happy
a couple minutes ago.
几分钟前你看起来很开心。
- You know what?
- What?
- 你知道吗?-
- I don't like your tone.
- CALEB: Mm-hmm.
什么?-我不喜欢你的语气。
- And I really don't like seeing
security camera footage of you
我真的不喜欢看到监控录像里你到处
fucking around
and leaving early.
乱搞然后提前离开。
I'm trying to run a business--
我正在努力经营一个生意
a profitable,
respectable business!
——一个有利可图的、体面的生意!-
- You're right,
this is a mini-mart.
你说得对，这是一个小型超市。
It's very serious. We sell,
what, 10 types of Funyuns
非常严重。我们卖10种洋葱和
and, like, a pickle in a sack?
一袋泡菜？-
- You know what,
don't fucking test me!
你知道吗，别他妈
I could fire you!
的考验我！我可以炒了你！
- Okay, Suzanne,
I can't lose this job.
苏珊娜，我不能丢了这份工作。
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- 真的?-嗯哼。
I need the minimum
wage that you pay me.
我需要你付给我的最低工资。
- Really?
- 真的?-
- Yeah, so, it won't
happen again, I swear.
是啊所以不会再发生了我发誓。
- I'm sorry?
- 你说什
- It won't
happen again, I swear.
么?-不会再发生了我发誓。
- Fine.
好吧。
- Cool.
酷。
- Can we also just agree that
我们能不能同意这里发生的一切都不
what happens in
here stays in here?
要说出去？你是说这里和这
- Do you mean what happened here
and, like, here,
里发生的事吗,
and, like, here?
还有，这里?-是的，
- Yeah, all of
it, and over there, right.
所有的，还有那边，对。
- Mm-hmm, yeah, no.
是啊不。
Secret's safe with me.
我会守口如瓶的。
- You promise?
- Sure.
- 你保证?-当然。
Can I leave now?
- Please.
我现在可以走了吗?-请吧。
- Thanks.
谢谢。
Oh.
哦。
You could be a little
nicer to her, you know?
你可以对她好一点，你知道吗
- So could you.
?-你也可以。
- You're
off by two cents.
你少了两分钱。
- DARA: Go.
去吧。
Just go.
走吧。
Well?
- I can't believe you like her.
怎么样?-我不敢相信你喜欢她。
She's, like, at least
five kinds of evil?
- 她至少有五种邪恶?-她恨我吗
- Does she hate me?
?-统计学上来说
- Hating you is
statistically possible,
恨你是有可能的,
and I have the math to prove it.
我有数学证明。
- Yeah, you failed math. Twice.
你数学不及格两次。
- This is a different
type of math.
这是一种不同的数学。
This is gay math.
这是同性恋的数学。
- Oh, some kid came
in looking for you?
- 哦有个孩子进来找
He bought kettle corn.
I think he's still outside.
你?-他买了爆米花我想他还在外面。
Are you hooking up with him?
你和他在一起吗?
- Gonna be right back.
-马上回来。
- [bell ringing]
[铃声]
- You do know that popcorn isn't
the only food group, right?
你知道爆米花不是唯一的食物吧？
- Jim's having a
cabaret show tomorrow.
吉姆明天有个歌舞表演。
Do you wanna go?
你想去吗
- It depends.
?-看情况。
Are you asking me out?
你是在约我出去吗
- Depends what you'd say.
?-那要看你说什么了。
- Maybe?
- Then maybe.
- 也许?-也许吧。
- I don't get off until eight.
我八点才下班。
- ESTHA: Show starts at nine.
- 演出九点开始。
- So just pick you up from here?
- I'll meet you there.
- 那就从这儿接你?-我们在那儿见。
- Okay, cool.
好吧。
- Is she your friend?
她是你的朋友吗？
- Yeah, she's kind
of my only one.
是啊她是我唯一的女人。
- I figured.
我想也是。
- How?
- 怎么说?
- You both say very
strange things.
-你们俩都说了很奇怪的话。
- MALE SINGER:
♪ Going toe to toe ♪
- 男歌手: “我
♪ Under the neon lights ♪
们要紧挨着脚趾”
♪ We're gonna-- ♪
♪在霓
- ♪
虹灯下我们要 -- ♪-♪
- Do you feel like
closing early tonight?
你今晚
- ♪
想早
- [rock music plays
from headphones]
点关门
- Dara!
吗！
Dara!
达拉
- [rock music playing]
！教我谎言，
♪ Teach me the lies,
teach me to win ♪
教我赢钱！哇，
- Whoa!
真是
- Wow, a vicious read.
恶毒的读法。
Make it up to me
with a close party.
用一个亲密的聚会来补偿我。
- I'm not feeling
so hot right now.
我现在不太舒服。
- That sounds like
a perfect excuse
这听起来像是关闭这
to shut this place down
and get absolutely blasted.
个地方，让它完全爆炸的完美借口。
- There's only 15 minutes left.
We should at least wait.
只剩下15分钟了，我们至少应该等等。
- You're right, we should.
你说得对，我们应该这么做。
- [Scissor Sisters
singing "Any Which Way"]
- [《剪刀姐妹》唱“ Any Which Way”]
- [both imitating
water gurgling]
[两人都模仿水声]
- ♪ I don't need a doctor ♪
我不需要医生
♪ Just a simple look or garter ♪
只是一个简单的外观或者吊袜带
♪ To slide to my
side so civilly ♪
如此文明地滑到我身边
♪ No talk of commitment ♪
没有承诺的谈话
♪ When I receive a shipment ♪
当我收到货物时
♪ Oh, I need express delivery ♪
我需要快递
♪ Any which way, any which way ♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向
♪ You better take me
any which way you can ♪
你最好带我走任何你能走的路
♪ Any which way,
any which way ♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向
♪ You better take me
any which way you can ♪
你最好带我走任何你能走的路
- [Caleb groaning]
- [Dara laughing]
- [迦勒呻吟]-[达拉笑]
- ♪ You know, baby ♪
你知道，宝贝
♪ When I was taking my pantyhose
out of their egg this evening ♪
今晚当我从他们的蛋里拿出我的裤袜时
♪ I thought, I'm gonna
find that man that has ♪
我想，我要找到那个男人
♪ The right shade
of bottled tan ♪
恰到好处的瓶装棕褐色
♪ A man that smells like
cocoa butter and cash ♪
一个闻起来像可可油和现金的男人
♪ Take me anyway you like it ♪
带我去你喜欢的地方吧
♪ In front of the fireplace ♪
在壁炉前面
♪ In front of your yacht ♪
在你的游艇前面
♪ In front of my parents ♪
在我父母面前
♪ I don't give a damn,
baby, just take me ♪
我不在乎，宝贝，带我走吧
♪ Any which way, any which way ♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向
♪ Any which way you can ♪
任何方式你都可以
♪ Any which way, any which way ♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向
♪ Any which way you can ♪
任何方式你都可以
♪ Any which way, any which way ♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向
♪ Any which way you can ♪
任何方式你都可以
♪ Any which way,
any which way you can ♪♪
随便哪个方向，随便哪个方向你都可以
- [vomiting]
- [呕吐]
- [Caleb belching]
- [ Caleb 打嗝]-
- [Dara mumbling]
[ Dara 咕哝]
What's wrong?
怎么了?
Are you gonna vomit too?
你也要吐吗。
- Mm-mm.
- Okay.
- Maybe.
- 好吧-也许吧。
You think we'll ever find
other people to do this with?
你觉得我们会找到其他人一起
- Why do we need other people?
做这个吗？我
- No, like--
们为什么需
like a boyfriend or a girlfriend
or maybe somebody in-between.
要其他人？不是男朋友女朋友或者中间人。
Like, somebody who
wants to do dumb shit
比如，有人想做蠢事
who also wants to make out.
，但同时又想亲热。
- Oh.
- Mm.
- 哦-嗯。
- Yeah.
是啊。
For sure.
当然。
- What if that's
harder for me now?
- 如果这对我来
- It won't be.
说更难呢?-不会的。
- Yeah, but what if it is?
- 是的，但如果是呢
- No.
?-不。
It won't be.
不会的。
And until then,
you got me, bitch.
在那之前，你还有我，贱人。
- PEDRO: Everything about
my life is uncertain.
我的生活充满了不确定性。
I'm totally stressed out
because of my health,
因为我的健康我压力很大,
and I'm totally stressed
out because of work,
工作压力太大了,
and I don't know
what I want to do.
我不知道我想做什么。
- Just call me and tell me.
给我打电话告诉我。
That's the only thing
I've ever asked for.
这是我唯一的要求。
- ♪
- Hey, Caleb?
- 嘿 Ca
Can I run something by you?
leb? 我能跟你说点
- Totally.
事吗?-当然。
- VALERIE: Okay,
how's this sound?
瓦莱丽: 好的，这个听起来怎
"When I first started teaching
here back in the late 1800s"...
么样? “当我在19世纪末开始在这里教书的时候”..。
Pause for laughs.
停下来笑一笑。
"The only gender studies
course was worth half a credit
“唯一一门性别研究课程只值半个学分，
and met in what is now
the woman's bathroom."
而且是在现在的女厕所里开设的。”好了
- Okay, Joan Rivers,
，琼 · 里弗斯,
is this a guest lecture
or an HBO special?
这是客座讲座还是 HBO 特别节目？
Grandma?
奶奶? 你还好吗
You good?
?-是的，
- Yeah, yeah, less
Joan Rivers, got it.
是的，少说点琼 · 里弗斯，明白了。
Thanks a lot, honey.
非常感谢，亲爱的。
- [phone buzzing]
看看你
- PHONE: Look at
your phone, bitch!
的手机，婊子！
- ♪
- JIM: And when a hot redhead
walks down the street,
当一个红发辣妹走在街上,
do you also imagine
God knocking over
你能想象上帝
a bottle of Sriracha?
打翻了一瓶
- [audience laughing]
拉差酱吗？我想是
- JIM: Well, I think
it's time for a song.
时候唱首歌了。
This is a special request
from an audience member
这是第三排的观众提
in the third row.
出的特殊要求。
Everyone wave hi to Estha!
大家向 Esth
- [audience applauding]
a 挥
- ♪
手!-[观众鼓掌]-
♪ Ground control
to Major Tom ♪
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校
♪
♪ Ground control to Major Tom ♪
地面控制呼叫汤姆少校
♪
♪ Take your protein pills
and put your helmet on ♪
带上你的蛋白质药丸，戴上你的头盔
♪
- Can you earn a living
from taking photographs?
你能靠拍照谋生吗？
Isn't very practical.
不是很实际。
- Practicality is very 2010.
- 实用性是非常2010年。
I was gonna go to
college in New York,
我本来要去纽约上大学,
take a bunch of photos,
overdose on ramen.
拍了很多照片，吃了很多拉面。
How about you?
Where you going next year?
你呢? 明年要去哪里?-
- Georgia Tech.
佐治亚理工学院。
- Atlanta.
亚特兰大。
Fancy.
真不错。
You're excited?
你很兴奋?-
- It's hard to think of
anything past this summer.
这个夏天以后很难想起任何事情。
- Do you ever, like,
wonder what you would do
- 你有没有想过如果测试结果出来
if the test came back--
- No.
你会怎么做-没有。
I try not to.
我尽量不这么做。
- Yeah, uh, me either.
我也是。
I mean, I know you're
supposed to be fine
我的意思是，我知道你应
if you take all the
shit you're supposed to.
该没事，如果你吃了所有你应该吃的东西。
At this point, you'd have worse
luck with cancer, but, like...
在这一点上，你得癌症的运气会更差，但是，就像..。
Still kinda wish it
was something else.
还是有点希望是别的什么。
Like, anything else.
比如，其他的。
- You'd rather have cancer?
- 你宁愿得
- I don't know
about that, but, um...
癌症?-我不知道但是..。
Yeah, I just--at least then
I wouldn't feel like it was--
是的，我只是，至少那样我就不
- ESTHA: Your fault.
会觉得...-你的错。
- Anyways, are you, um--
are you gonna go to sleep
- 不管怎样你回
when you get home, or--
- Am I going home?
家后要睡觉吗-我要回家吗？
Are we gonna get in trouble?
- 我们会有麻
- It's always a possibility.
烦吗?-总是有可能的。
- Is this your temple?
- 这是你的庙吗
- CALEB: Yeah, it used to be.
?-是的，以前是。
- What happened?
- 发生了什么?
- Um, the artist formerly known
as my mother married the rabbi,
-艺术家以前的名字是我妈妈嫁给了拉比,
and they're assholes,
so I stopped going.
他们都是混蛋所以我不去了。
- You really shouldn't
talk about her like that.
你真的不应该那样说她。
She's still your mom.
她还是你妈妈。
- CALEB: Yeah, but, like,
- 是的，但是，就像,
moms aren't supposed to forget
to pick you up
妈妈们不应该忘记在你
from band practice right after
your dad died
爸爸去世后，去乐队排练
'cause she's too busy
trying to find a new husband.
时接你，因为她正忙着找新丈夫。
Moms aren't supposed
to make you move in
妈妈们不应该让你搬去和奶奶一起住，
with your grandma because
your big old gay lifestyle
因为你那古老的同性恋生活方式
doesn't sit too well
with the rabbi's mezuzah.
不适合犹太教教士的 mezuzah。
Moms aren't supposed
to treat you
妈妈们不
like a total and
complete stranger.
应该把你当成一个完全的陌生人。
- What's a mezuzah?
- mezuzah 是什么?-就像
- It's like this thing
you nail to your house.
你钉在房子上的东西。
It's got the Bible in it.
里面有圣经。
Come on, this jungle gym
is gonna blow your mind.
来吧，这个攀登架会让你大吃一惊的。
- ♪
- I lost two teeth falling
off of this jungle gym.
我从攀登架上掉了两颗牙。
Tooth fairy was supposed
to give me 20 bucks.
牙仙应该给我20块钱的。
Instead, I got two carrots
and a pack of Chiclets.
相反，我得到了两个胡萝卜和一包糖果。
- That's upsetting?
- No, it was pretty funny.
- 这让你心烦意乱?-不，这很有趣。
My dad did dumb shit
like that all the time.
我爸爸经常干这种蠢事。
Um, I had my first
kiss under this bridge
我和 Jordan Stei
with Jordan Stein.
n 在桥下初吻。
Jordan smelled like applesauce.
Needless to say, I was smitten.
乔丹闻起来像苹果酱，不用说，我被迷住了。
- What happened to him?
- Jordan was a girl.
- 他怎么了?-Jordan 是个女孩。
- I meant your dad.
我是说你爸爸。
- Oh.
哦。
Um, he had a heart attack.
他心脏病发作。
I once peed down this slide.
我有一次在滑梯上尿尿。
Okay, I'm lying.
I peed down this slide a lot.
好吧，我撒谎了，我在这个滑梯上撒了很多尿。
- That must've been hard.
那一定很痛苦。
- No, I've got awesome pee aim.
不，我的尿尿准确度很棒。
- I was talking about your dad.
我说的是你爸爸。
- I know.
我知道。
- When did he, uh--
- [thunder booming]
- 他什么时候...-我们得找个
- We should take cover.
I think it's gonna rain.
地方躲起来，要下雨了。
- [rain piddling]
[雨水撒尿]
- I think I'm sitting
on a spider.
我想我正坐在一只蜘蛛上。
- It's a playground
rite of passage.
这是一个游乐场的仪式。
I think you're gonna be fine.
我想你会没事的。
- I can't believe
this is outside the place
我不敢相信这里是
where you pray.
你祈祷的地方。
- Yep, there's a
sanctuary in there.
是的，那里有个避难所。
It's also a catering
hall and a preschool.
它还是一个餐饮大厅和一个幼儿园。
We're nothing if not
an economical people.
如果我们不是一个节俭的民族，我们什么都不是。
- Do you like being Jewish?
- 你喜欢当犹太人吗?-这是个很
- It's a loaded question.
有深度的问题。
Um, leaning toward yes.
倾向于是。
There's, like, six
types of Jewish people,
犹太人大概有六种,
and I wanna say two
are pretty fierce.
我想说有两个非常厉害。
Do you like being Hindu?
你喜欢做印度
- Who said I was Hindu?
教徒吗？谁说我是印度教徒？- 天啊
- Oh my god, I'm so sorry--
，我很抱歉.
- I'm just kidding.
..-我开玩笑的。
I'm Hindu.
我是印度教徒。
- [chuckles]
[笑声]
- I, uh...
我..。
It's getting late.
时间不早了。
- ♪
- BENNY: Where you going?
- Work.
- 本尼: 你去哪里?-工作。
- Where you really going?
- 你到底要去哪
- I'm gonna go do some
drugs, graffiti buildings,
儿?-我要去吸毒涂鸦建筑,
TP the principal's house.
- Caleb.
封锁校长家-Caleb。
- Benny, could we
not do this now, please?
班尼，我们现在能不能不谈这个
- "The Young and The Sexless?"
？- “年轻人和性冷淡者?”
- Where did you find that?
- On the floor.
你在哪儿找到的？- 在地板上。
- I'm doing a photo project.
我在做一个摄影项目。
Gay men in crisis, the pos
community, homeless youth,
危机中的同性恋社区无家可归的年轻人,
those who can't dress
for their body type.
那些不能根据自己的体型穿衣的人。
- You're lying.
- I'm not lying.
- 你撒谎-我没撒谎。
- Are you gonna tell her?
Or am I?
- 你要告诉她吗? 还是我来?
- You know, this is actually
none of your business.
-其实这不关你的事。
- Excuse me?
- 什么?
- We both know
that you only pretend
-我们都知道
to give a shit about me
because you have to...for her.
你假装在乎我是因为你必须... 为了她。
- Do you know me?
你认识我吗？
Have we met?
我们见过吗？现
Now I've spent the last
taking you out for
sleepovers and band practice
带你出去过夜，去乐队
and off the floor
because your daddy died.
排练，因为你爸爸去世了。
I could be buying pina coladas
and the daiquiris,
我可以去买凤梨汁和鸡尾酒,
some loose poker, but I
decided to spend it on you,
一些扑克牌但我决定把钱花在你身上,
because we do belong together.
因为我们是天生一对。
If you don't tell her, I will,
because you're just a kid.
如果你不告诉她，我会的，因为你只是个孩子。
You shouldn't do this alone.
你不应该一个人做这件事。
- ♪
♪
- DR. DIAZ: Caleb?
Caleb? 你
What's new with you?
有什么新鲜事吗？
- Oh, I've been amazing.
我一直都很棒。
Things have been
looking up for me.
一切都在向好的方向发展。
Um, my job is awesome.
我的工作棒极了。
I had a conversation
with my boss.
我和我的老板谈了一下。
We're gonna take things to the
next level professionally.
我们要把事情发展到更高的专业水平。
I'm very excited about that.
我对此感到非常兴奋。
Kinda Zen about the whole thing.
对整个事情都有点禅意。
I think it's this new
sleep regiment I'm on.
我想是因为我参加了一个新的睡眠团。
Also, I've been riding
my bike everywhere,
还有，我骑着自行车到处跑,
so I'm like--like
saving the planet
所以我既要拯救地球
and engaging my core
at the same time.
又要同时投入我的核心。
- DR. DIAZ: That's great, Caleb.
太好了，凯莱布。
- ♪
- ♪-
- [repeated thunking]
[不断的打雷]
- [door creaking]
[门吱吱作响]
- Did you just get here?
- Unfortunately.
- 你刚到吗?-不幸的是。
- Dude, I called you,
like, twice this morning.
伙计我今天早上给你打了两次电话。
- Yeah, I woke up late.
Suzanne here?
- 我起晚了 Suzanne
- No, she's with that penis.
在吗?-不她和那个阴茎在一起。
- CALEB: Thank God.
- CALEB: 谢天谢地。
- How are you?
- 你好
- Alive.
吗?-还活着。
I get test results tomorrow.
我明天拿到检查结果。
- Alright?
- 好吗? 想一起玩吗?
Wanna hang?
Help take your mind off of it?
帮你忘掉这些? 我
I'm supposed to work,
要工作,
but it's not like
anyone needs me here.
但这里没人需要我。
- I'm good, don't worry.
我很好，别担心。
- I'm not worried,
我不担心,
I just thought you
might want some company.
我只是觉得你可能需要人陪。
- I have plans.
我有安排了。
- With who?
- 和谁?-一
- A friend.
个朋友。
- What friend?
什
- ♪
么朋友
- Wow, this place is
definitely a...choice.
这地方绝对是个不错的选择。
Where is everybody?
大家都去哪儿了?-我
- We close down
Monday for cleaning.
们星期一停业打扫。
- We?
- 我们?
- You're not the
only one with a job.
-你不是唯一有工作的人。
- ♪
在接下来的42
- Everything you see can be
yours for the next 42 minutes.
分钟里你看到的一切都是你的。
- You're full of surprises.
你真是充满惊喜。
- I thought a little escape
might help you calm down.
我想逃避一下也许能让你冷静下来。
- Unless the rides
are made of Xanax,
除非游乐设施是用阿普唑仑做的,
I don't think that's possible.
- Can you just relax?
我觉得这不可能-你能放松
For me?
点吗? 为了我？
- [metal clanging]
欢迎来到
- Welcome to the popcorn stand.
爆米花摊。
Would you like it
sweet or salty?
你喜欢甜的还是咸的?-关于你
- Every single question
I've ever had about you
的每一个问题我都
has just been answered.
已经回答了。
- They say if
you do what you love,
他们说如果你做自己喜欢的事,
you never work a
day in your life.
你这辈子从来没工作过。
- Okay, but
I'm almost positive
好吧但我几乎可以肯定他
they didn't mean popping corn.
们说的不是爆玉米。
- That's where you're wrong.
It's the best.
- 这你就错了-这是最好的。
Back home, we used to go to
在家乡，我们经常在
the American movie
theater on Sundays.
星期天去美国电影院。
I'd be excited to go all week.
我整个星期都很兴奋。
They played the classics like
"Breakfast at Tiffany's"
他们演奏的经典曲目有《蒂凡尼
or "A Star is Born" or--
的早餐》、《天生的明星
- Oh, which version?
- There's more than one?
》或——-哦，哪个版本？不止一
- Okay, I'm gonna
pretend you're joking.
个？好吧我假装你在开玩笑。
- It didn't matter what
the movie was anyway.
不管是什么电影。
It just would take
me out of my head.
这只会让我忘记一切。
Anytime I felt depressed,
I'd, uh, go back into my pockets
每当我感到沮丧的时候，我就会，呃，回到我的口袋里，
and take the leftover
popcorn and eat it,
把剩下的爆米花吃掉,
and I was back watching
Holly Golightly and her cat.
我回来看霍莉 · 戈莱特利和她的猫。
- Now you can get out of
your head whenever you want,
现在你想什么时候走都可以,
so maybe try eating a vegetable.
也许你可以试试吃蔬菜。
- I still like eating it.
It helps me not be--
- 我还是喜欢吃它它能帮我不
- Sad?
再...-悲伤
- Present.
?-礼物。
What next?
接下来呢？
- ♪ [Vampire Weekend
singing "White Sky"]
“吸血鬼周末”唱“白天”
- Go!
走！
- ♪ An ancient business, a
modern piece of glasswork ♪
一件古老的事业，一件现代的玻璃作品
♪ Down on the corner ♪
在下面的角落
♪ That you walk each
day in passing ♪
你每天都在路上行走
♪ The whole immortal
corporation's ♪
♪整个不朽的公司
♪ Given its permission ♪
给它许可
- Tom?
汤姆？
Can you operate the
drop for me and my--
你能帮我和我的..
me and my cousin?
我和我表妹？
- ♪ A little stairway, a
little piece of carpet ♪
一段楼梯，一小块地毯
♪ A pair of mirrors that
are facing one another ♪
一对面对面的镜子
♪ Out in both directions,
a thousand little Julias ♪
从两个方向出去，一千个小朱利亚
♪ That come together in
the middle of Manhattan ♪
它们在曼哈顿的中心汇聚
♪ You waited since lunch ♪
你从午饭就开始等了
♪ It all comes at once ♪
它一下子就来了
♪ Oh, oh, ooh ooh ooh ♪
噢，噢，噢，噢，噢
♪ Oh, oh, ooh ♪♪
噢，噢，噢
- Where are you going?
- 你要去哪儿
- TOM: It's stuck!
Gotta call maintenance.
?-卡住了! 得打电话给维修部。
- [birds cawing]
- 你没
- Are you all right?
事吧?-没事。
- Yeah.
- [roller coaster creaking]
- [云霄
- ♪
飞车吱吱声] -
- Dara?
达拉? 迦勒告
Caleb tells me
you're a great cook.
诉我你是个很棒的厨师。
What do you like to make?
你喜欢做什
- Food.
么?-食物。
[whispers] I make food.
我做饭。
- [door opening]
- Thank God.
谢天谢地。
- Happy to see me?
- What's the verdict?
- 见到我高兴吗?-结果如何
- DR. DIAZ: Your 30-day antibody
test came back negative.
?-你30天的抗体测试结果呈阴性。
- So far, so good, right?
- 目前为止还不错吧?
- DR. DIAZ: So far.
-目前为止。
I will see you back here
on day 60 and day 90.
我们第60天和第90天再见。
- Thanks for coming
with me today.
谢谢你今天陪我来。
- Duh.
- Sure.
- 废话-当然。
- Oh, shit, I never thought
I'd need a third seat.
该死，我从没想过我还需要第三个座位。
Let's take the bus.
The bus is cool.
我们坐公共汽车吧。公共汽车很酷。
- No, it's chill. Um, I told
Suzanne I'd help her out
没事我跟苏珊娜说一小时后
at the store in an hour.
去店里帮忙。
- Ew. You don't work today.
你今天不上班。
- I don't know. She asked
if I wanted overtime, so--
- 我不知道她问我要不要加班所以
- Okay, don't do
anything I wouldn't do,
...-好吧别做我不会做的事,
so don't do anything.
所以什么都别做。
Hey.
嘿。
Look, Benny, I know
I've been a dick lately,
听着 Benny 我知道我最近很混蛋,
and I just wanted to
say I'm really sorry.
我只想说我真的很抱歉。
It's, like, a lot for
me, and I don't know how
这对我来说太多了，
I'm gonna tell her, but--
我不知道该怎么告诉她，
- VALERIE: Tell her what?
但是 ---瓦莱丽: 告诉她什么？
Well, somebody
better say something.
最好有人说点什么。
Somebody, anybody,
任何人，任何人,
before I burn this
house to the ground.
在我把这房子烧成灰烬之前。
What?
- 什么? 发
What's going on?
生什么事
- Okay, okay, um...
了?-好的好的呃..。
Lately, I've been going
through this thing.
最近，我一直在经历这件事。
I met a guy after Don
dumped me and we, you know,
Don 甩了我之后我遇到了一个男的,
and the condom ripped and
it turns out he has HIV.
避孕套破了，结果他感染了艾滋病。
But I don't know if I have it.
但我不知道我有没有。
I don't think I have it.
我想我没有。
I might not have it, you know,
and I have to wait until
我可能没有，你知道，我必须等
the end of summer
to find out if I do.
到夏天结束才能知道我是否有。
And that's why I've been
kind of a bitch lately.
这就是为什么我最近有点像个婊子。
Can you please say something?
你能说点什么吗
- Why didn't you tell me sooner?
？你为什么不早
- I didn't want to freak
you out after everything.
点告诉我？我不想吓到你。
Benny tried to get me
to tell you, but, like,
Benny 想让我告诉你但是,
I couldn't.
我做不到。
- You could never
freak me out, Caleb,
你吓不倒我的 Caleb,
although you sure
keep trying to.
尽管你一直在努力。
- Well, it's
just, like, I mean,
只是我是说,
telling you just makes
the whole thing feel real,
告诉你只会让整件事感觉很真实,
and I was just totally
hoping it would be imaginary.
我只是希望那是想象出来的。
- The only thing that's
real is this right here,
唯一真实的东西就是这个,
you and me, no?
你和我，不是吗? 现在给
Now give me a hug.
我一个拥抱。
- Okay, I can't breathe.
Grandma?
- 好吧，我喘不过气了，奶奶
- VALERIE: If you ever hide
?-瓦莱丽:
anything like this
from me again,
如果你再对我隐瞒这种事,
you won't have to worry
about getting sick
你不用担心生病因为我
because I will throttle
you with my bare hands,
会赤手空拳掐死你,
you understand what
I'm saying to you?
- 你明白我说的
- Yes.
话吗?-明白。
- VALERIE: Good.
瓦莱丽: 很好。
- [phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
- [phone buzzing]
- [Kidz Bop Kids singing
"DJ Got Us Falling In Love"]
- [ Kidz Bop Kids 演唱“ DJ Got Us Falling In Love”]
♪ Kidz Bop ♪
♪ Yeah, man ♪
对，伙计
♪ So we back in the club ♪
于是我们回到俱乐部
- Hey. Everything okay?
一切都好吗？
- Yes. Why are we whispering?
是的，我们为什么要小声说话？
- I'm at home.
我在家。
- Oh, okay, cool.
好吧。
- ESTHA: What's up?
- 怎
- Um...
么了?-呃..。
I told her.
我告诉她。
- Told her what?
- 告诉
- My grandma. About everything.
她什么?-我奶奶所有的事。
- How did it go?
- 进展如
- Yeah, I mean,
considering I felt that
何?-是啊我是
the news might kill
her, it was pretty okay.
说考虑到我觉得这个消息可能会害死她所以还不错。
- You're lucky.
- Am I on speaker?
- 你真幸运-我开了扬声器吗?
I can't hear you
over the Kidz Bop.
我听不清你说什么。
- I said,
okay, that's great.
- 我说，好的，太好了。
I, uh--I can't talk now.
I'll see you tonight.
我现在不方便说话晚上见。
- ♪
- Did you not
want to tell me because
你不想告诉我是因为你知道
you knew it'd be even harder
for me to sell this place?
我更难卖掉这个地方吗？我知道 Cal
- I know you're
upset about Caleb.
eb 的事让你很难过。
- No, no, I'm not
upset about Caleb!
不，不，我没有因为
I'm furious with you,
asshole, for lying to me!
Caleb 的事生气！我对你很生气，混蛋
Caleb is fine. He's just--
，因为你对我撒谎！C
He's going to be fine.
aleb 没事。他会没事的。
He's gonna be fine.
他会没事的。
He's gonna be fine. He's--
他会没事的，
He's gonna be fine.
他会没事的。
[sobbing]
卡莱布?
- DR. DIAZ: Caleb? You with us?
你在吗？
- Feels like all
I do is worry her.
我觉得我只会让她担心。
After my dad died,
我爸爸死后,
she convinced herself that
she's responsible for me,
她说服自己要对我负责,
and she feels guilty
that I ended up here,
她为我来到这里而感到内疚,
which makes me feel even
guiltier than I already did.
这让我觉得比以前更内疚了。
Being Jewish is really
hard, basically.
基本上，成为犹太人真的很难。
- You did the right thing.
你做得对。
It's good to have someone
to talk to at home.
在家里有人聊天是件好事。
And, Estha?
How are things going with you?
- 还有，伊斯塔? 你怎么样
- Um, they've been better.
了?-嗯，好多了。
I, um...
我呃..。
I, um, find out soon,
我很快就会知道了,
and every hour feels like a day.
I...
每一个小时都像一天一样我..。
I still don't know what
my dad will do if, uh--
我还是不知道我爸爸会怎么做
I'm everything to them, the...
如果我是他们的一切。
perfect son, the one they to
talk to their friends about,
完美的儿子，他们可以和朋友谈论的那个,
the salutatorian,
致辞代表,
the one that they scram out
to lunch every single Sunday.
他们每个星期天都会出去吃午饭。
They love the son
I let them see.
他们爱我让他们看到的儿子。
But then there's this
other part of me, right...
但还有另外一部分的我，对吧..。
the part I keep hidden...
我隐藏的那部分..。
and I keep trying so hard
to be perfect because
我一直努力追求完美因为我觉得他们
I think they'd hate
that other part of me.
会讨厌我的另一面。
But if I do end up having this,
I know I'll have to tell them.
但是如果我最终得到了这个，我知道我必须告诉他们。
I just don't wanna
be here anymore.
我只是不想再待在这里了。
I, uh--I'll go back.
我... 我回去。
I'd even go forward. It's here.
我甚至可以往前走，就在这里。
Here is where I'm having an
issue, where I can't even
这就是我的问题所在，我甚至不
watch the TV with my parents
without them thinking that
能和我的父母一起看电视，除非
they know it's there, that
they can smell it on me.
他们认为他们知道电视在那里，他们能在我身上闻到电视的味道。
- DR. DIAZ: Smell what on you?
你身上有什么味道？
- Shame.
真可惜。
- ♪
♪
- [phone ringing]
看看你
- PHONE: Look at
your phone, bitch!
的手机
- [phone ringing]
，婊子。
- Hi.
- Happy Fourth, fool.
第四节快乐傻瓜。
Are we gonna stoned
and watch "Spiders From Mars"
我们是不是要像去年那样吸毒
like last year? I can score some
然后看“火星蜘蛛”? 我
environmentally-friendly
fireworks.
可以弄到一些环保烟花。
- No, I can't, I'm sorry.
There's something I have to do.
不，我不能，对不起，我有些事情必须要做。
- DARA: You with that kid again?
- His name is Estha.
- 你又和那孩子在一起?-他叫 Estha。
- All right, whatever.
好吧随便了。
I gotta tell you something
about Suzanne later, though.
不过我稍后会告诉你一些关于苏珊娜的事。
- CALEB: Why? What happened?
- 为什么? 发生什
- She said she loved me.
么事了?-她说她爱我。
That she fucking loved me.
她他妈的爱我。
- SUZANNE: Sorry, somebody's
gotta make a living
苏珊: 对不起
in this family right now!
，现在总得有人在这个家里谋生
- Yeah, that's why she
asked me to work overtime.
吧！是啊所以她让我加班。
After we hooked up,
我们在一起之后,
she couldn't stop thinking
about me. How sick is that?
她无法停止想我。这有多变态?-达拉
- CALEB: Dara, I really
gotta go, I'm sorry.
，我真的得走了，对不起。
I'll call you back later.
- Well--
我一会儿再打给你。
- Are you ready to go?
-嗯 ---你
- Where?
准备好走
- ♪
了吗?-去哪儿?-
- So these are the fireworks?
- 这些就是烟花
- Hey, it's the best I could do.
?-我只能做到这样了。
- ♪
- Ooh!
哦！
Big, scary, ooh!
大，可怕，哦！
- ♪
- FEMALE SINGER:
♪ Accidental lover ♪
偶然的爱人
♪ What'd you do with
all my common sense ♪
你对我的常识做了什么
♪
♪ You came in undercover ♪
你进来卧底
♪ When I didn't
even want a friend ♪
当我甚至不需要朋友的时候
♪
♪ I'm tired of looking
like I'm dying ♪
我厌倦了看起来像要死的样子
♪ I know I can find
the silver lining ♪
我知道我能找到一线希望
♪ Like before ♪
像以前一样
♪
♪ Like before ♪
像以前一样
♪ And you got a funny
sense of timing ♪
你对时间的把握很有意思
♪ Showed up on the night
that I stopped trying ♪
在我停止尝试的那个夜晚出现
♪ Something more ♪
♪更多的东西♪
♪ You're something more ♪
你是更多的东西
♪ And I'm like, oh, sweet,
gotta think I'm in trouble ♪
我就像，哦，亲爱的，我觉得我有麻烦了
♪ Kinda make you wonder ♪
有点让你好奇
♪ What it's like
on the other side ♪
在另一边是什么样的
♪ And I'm like, baby ♪
我就像，宝贝
♪ Kinda drive me crazy ♪
有点让我疯狂
♪ I'm not one to save you ♪
我不是救你的人
♪ But I guess I
will really try ♪
但我想我真的会尝试
♪ Oh my, oh my ♪♪
噢，我的，噢，我的
- ESTHA: Thanks
for kidnapping me.
谢谢你绑架我。
- I'm a surprisingly
good kidnapper.
我绑架技术出奇的好。
Feel like I should be
more alarmed by that.
我觉得我应该对此更加警惕。
- ESTHA: I live so close to
the beach, but I never come.
我住得离海滩很近，但我从来没有来过。
- CALEB: Hm, congrats.
恭喜你。
You're officially
a true Floridian.
你正式成为佛罗里达人了。
Come on, being from
Florida isn't that bad.
拜托，来自佛罗里达也没那么糟。
It's gonna be okay, you know.
会没事的。
- You know it's not.
你知道不是的。
You know everything could
change after tomorrow.
你知道过了明天一切都会改变的。
- Do you know who
Pedro Zamora is?
- 你知道 Pedro Zamo
- I don't know any of the
people you talk about.
ra 是谁吗?-我不认识你说的任何人。
- Right.
对。
Well, basically, there was,
um, this TV show in the '90s
基本上90年代有个电视节目
called "The Real
World: San Francisco."
叫做《真实世界: 旧金山》
Seven complete strangers
七个完全陌生的人
move into a
poorly-decorated brownstone
搬进装修简陋的褐石屋
and annoy the shit
out of each other.
把对方惹毛了。
Pedro is one of those people.
佩德罗就是其中之一。
He was from here, actually.
实际上他是本地人。
He also was openly pos,
他也公开表示,
which was, like,
brutal at the time.
那时候真是太残忍了。
And no matter how much his
dumb roommate talked shit,
不管他那个蠢室友说了多少废话,
he still managed to be
the smartest, funniest,
他仍然是最聪明最有趣的,
finest motherfucker in the room.
这屋子里最好的混蛋。
- Did he make it?
他成功了吗？
- No.
没有。
But we will.
但我们会的。
- I don't want to live
with something that makes
我不想活在一个让
everyone in my life leave me.
我生命中的每个人都离开我的东西里。
- I won't leave you.
我不会离开你的。
- ♪
♪
- Isn't your grandma
gonna hear us?
- 你奶奶不会听到我们吗?
- What, no, she
can't hear anything.
-什么，不，她什么都听不到。
Um, we can be quiet,
though, just in case.
我们可以安静点以防万一。
- [The Drums singing
"Down By The Water"]
每个人都要爱
- ♪
一个人我应该
♪ Everybody's gotta
love someone ♪
吗？- ♪
- Should I?
-如
- ♪
果
- If you feel like
if you want to.
你想。
- ♪
- Caleb, this is bad.
- What?
- Caleb 这太糟了-什么?
This is fucking awesome.
这太他妈棒了。
- Yeah, I know, but,
we can't have sex.
我知道但我们不能做爱。
- [sighs]
定义一下性。
Define sex.
- ♪ We'll still be together ♪
我们还会在一起我知道这
♪ I know it's hard ♪
很难我知道这很
难但我理解你... 你在
♪ But I understand you... ♪
做什么？-
- What are you doing?
- CALEB: Relax.
迦勒: 放松。
- ♪ If you fall asleep
down by the water ♪
如果你在水边睡着了
♪ Baby, I'll carry... ♪
宝贝，我会带着..
- Oh, salty.
- [Caleb chuckling]
- 哦，咸咸的-[迦勒咯咯笑]
- ♪
♪ If you fall asleep
down by the water ♪
如果你在水边睡着了
♪ Baby, I'll carry
you all the way home ♪
宝贝，我会一路背你回家
♪
- Those are gonna be a
bitch to clean tomorrow.
那些明天就要清理了。
- Caleb.
卡莱布。
What are gonna do about this?
你打算怎么办
- What?
?-什么
- This.
?-这个。
- Um...
嗯..。
[moaning]
[呻吟]-♪-艾
- ♪
莎: 我感觉他
- ESTHA: I feel like
he's watching us.
在看着我们。
- He is.
是的。
But it's nothing he
hasn't seen before.
但这些都是他以前见过的。
Your parents gonna
wonder where you are?
你父母会想知道你在哪儿
- I don't care anymore.
吗?-我不在乎了。
- I'll come with you
tomorrow if you want.
如果你愿意，我明天和你一起去。
I'm pretty good company.
我是个很好的伙伴。
By that I mean I
will bring drugs.
我的意思是我会带上毒品。
- I'd rather go alone.
我宁愿一个人去。
Just don't know
what I'll do if...
只是不知道如果..。
- You'll take the medication,
and you'll be fine.
你会吃药的你会没事的。
- I don't think I'll make it.
我想我来不了了。
I think I'd just
rather not be here.
我想我宁愿不在这里。
- Don't say shit like that.
别说这种屁话。
It's not something
you joke about.
这不是你可以拿来开玩笑的。
- Oh, you're one to talk.
你还敢说。
- Have you ever lost anyone?
- 你失去过亲人吗?
- No.
-没有。
- Okay, well, with
all due respect,
好吧恕我直言,
you have no idea what it's like.
你不知道那是什么感觉。
Death is not, like, some
freedom from sadness
死亡并不是一种从悲伤、
or your parents or AIDS.
父母或艾滋病中解脱出来的自由。
It's no more bike rides,
it's no more movie nights,
不再有骑自行车的日子不再有电影之夜,
it's no more board games.
It's...
不再玩棋盘游戏了。
It's just nothing.
没什么。
Don't leave the people
who love you with nothing.
不要让爱你的人一无所有。
- If you love me, you
won't love me anymore.
如果你爱我，你就不会再爱我了。
- I'll ask you not
to speak for me. Thanks.
- 我请你不要为我说话-谢谢。
- [birds singing]
[鸟儿歌唱]
- ♪
- [bell ringing]
[铃声]
- Where's Suzanne?
- 苏珊娜呢?-
- She left.
她走了。
Yeah, something about
a dog having worms,
好像是狗身上长了虫子,
or worms having a dog, I don't
know. It sounded really gross.
或者虫子养狗我不知道听起来真恶心。
- Where is she?
她在哪儿？我刚告诉
- Hm, I just told you, sir, she
left. I mean, She's no longer--
你了，先生，她走了。我的意思是，她不再——-(苏珊娜咯
- [Suzanne giggling]
- --here.
咯笑)-——在这里。
- SUZANNE: Oh, oops, my bad!
- 苏珊: 哦，糟糕，我的错!-嗯
- Um, that's for
employees only back there.
，那是给那里的员工的。
- [Suzanne and Dara giggling]
- [苏珊娜和达拉傻笑
- Move.
- No.
]-让开-不。
- Move.
- No! [groans]
- 走开-不!-苏珊: 哈利!-他妈的怎么了
- SUZANNE: Harry!
- HARRY: What the fuck, Suzanne?
，苏珊?-苏珊: 听着，哈利，不是
- SUZANNE: Look, Harry, it's
not--just please calm down.
-- 请冷静下来。
It's not what you think.
She was helping me--
不是你想的那样她在帮我
- Helping you what?
Find your tits?
帮你什么? 找你的奶子？
- Yeah, I was helping her find
my tits! No, I, we were--
- 是啊我在帮她找我的咪咪!-不我我们..
- She's a kid!
- SUZANNE: She's not a kid!
- 她是个孩子!-她不是孩子！
- Actually, I'm 18.
- She's 18!
- 事实上我18岁了-她18岁了！
She's not a kid!
她不是小孩子了！
- HARRY: What am I
gonna tell Riley?
我要怎么跟莱利说？
- SUZANNE: Riley? Why do you
have to tell Riley anything?
赖利? 你为什么要告诉赖利任何事？
This is between you and me!
This is nothing!
这是你我之间的事! 这没什么！
Okay, it's nothing.
好吧没什么。
It's really just a stupid, big
fat nothing! There's nothing.
这真的只是一个愚蠢的，又大又空的东西! 什么都没有。
- Ah, uh, we're--
我们完事了。
We're done.
- Henry.
亨利。
I'm sorry, I--
对不起，我..
Henry!
亨利！
Come back!
回来!-
- [bell ringing]
呼!
- Hoo!
那太他
That was fucking crazy.
妈疯狂了。
- Yeah.
是啊。
She left.
她离开了。
Can't believe she left.
真不敢相信她走了。
- Dude, her
fucking husband
伙计，她那该死的丈夫
just almost Scott Petersoned me.
Are you okay?
我差点被斯科特 · 彼得上了你还好吗？
- Oh, so now you give
a shit about my life?
现在你开始关心我的生活了？
Because it's suddenly
dramatic enough for you?
因为对你来说突然变得足够戏剧化了？
- What the fuck is your problem?
你他妈的有什么毛病？
- My problem?
- Yeah.
- 我的问题?-是的。
- Caleb, what the
hell is your problem?
- Caleb 你到底有什么毛病
Banging weird dudes and
ditching me for that loser?
? 和怪人上床然后为了那个窝囊废甩了我?-
- Okay, Dara?
Take a second,
好了 Dara? 等一下,
and can you stop, like,
pretending to understand
你能不能别再假
the shitstorm that's become
my life, because you don't.
装理解我的生活，因为你不理解。
- But I wanted to, Caleb.
但我想这么做 Caleb。
But you don't give a shit.
但你一点都不在乎。
So, I'm done.
所以，我不干了。
Yeah, if you want to be sick
with someone else, fine.
是啊，如果你想和别人一起生病，没问题。
Go be sick with someone else.
去和别人一起生病吧。
- [bell ringing]
[铃声]
- [Perfume Genius
singing "Whole Life"]
- [香水天才演唱“整个生活”]
♪ Half of my whole life ♪
我生命的一半
♪ Is gone ♪
已经走了
♪
♪ Let it drift ♪
让它漂移吧
♪ And wash away ♪
把它冲走
♪
♪ It was just a dream ♪
那只是一个梦
♪ I had ♪
我有
♪
♪ It was just a dream ♪
那只是一个梦
♪
- Negative again.
- 又是阴性。
- Oh, fuck.
哦，妈的。
Can that just be it?
仅此而已吗？我真的需要再等
Like, do I really have
to wait another month?
一个月吗？我告
- I'm telling you,
you're going to be okay.
诉你，你会没事的。
- ♪ Half of my whole life ♪
♪我生命的一半
♪ Is done ♪
♪已
♪
经完成♪♪希瑟收集♪在
♪ Heather gathers ♪
它的位置♪
♪ In its place ♪
♪-嗨，我是泰勒,
- CALEB: Hey, this is Taylor,
calling you for the
five millionth time
我给你打了五百万次电话
to let you know that I've
written a song about you.
告诉你我为你写了一首歌。
It's called "Pick up
the phone, bitch."
叫做”接电话贱人”嘿。我只是
Hey. I just wanna know--
想知道 ---女人:
- WOMAN: This mailbox is full
这个邮箱
and cannot accept any messages
at this time. Good-bye.
已经满了，现在不能接受任何信息。再见。
- ♪ Leave them ♪
放开他们
♪ Behind ♪♪
♪后面♪
- FEMALE SINGER: ♪ Matchmaker,
matchmaker, make me a match ♪
媒人，媒人，帮我牵线搭桥
♪ Find me a find,
catch me a catch ♪
给我一个发现，给我一个发现
♪ Night after night in
the dark, I'm alone ♪
夜复一夜在黑暗中，我是孤独的
♪ So find me a match of my own ♪
给我找一根属于我自己的火柴
- Um, I'm gonna
head out for a bit.
我要出去一下。
- Oh, you know, Benny's
gonna be out late tonight.
你知道的 Benny 今晚会很晚回来。
He's playing poker.
他在玩扑克。
I thought it would
be a good time for us
我觉得现在是时候把
to put your portfolio together.
你的作品集放在一起了。
- CALEB: Yeah, I'm not doing
the portfolio any more.
- CALEB: 是的，我不再做投资组合了。
- Why not?
- 为什么
- Because I don't
want to, because I suck.
?-因为我不想因为我很烂。
Also, I don't think
I wanna go anymore.
还有，我不想再去了。
- Oh, wait just a minute here.
Stay right there.
哦，等一下，呆在那儿别动。
Now this is your dream school.
You're going.
这是你梦寐以求的学校。
- I'm not going.
我不去。
- VALERIE: Oh, I'm not
gonna let you do this.
瓦莱丽: 哦，我不会让你这么做的。
I'm not gonna let you throw
away everything you worked for!
我不会让你放弃你所有的努力！你
- Okay, just because
you couldn't save Dad
救不了爸爸不代表
doesn't mean you have
to try and save me.
你也要救我。
- That's not fair.
这不公平。
- I know we're not allowed to
talk about him, but that's true.
我知道我们不能谈论他但这是事实。
- Have you
thought at all about
你有没有想过这对
what this is like for me,
who's responsible for you?
我来说意味着什么，谁对你负责？
I can't talk about your
father because it'd kill me.
我不能谈论你的父亲，因为那会杀了我。
And then who would be
here to take care of you?
那么谁会在这里照顾你呢?-我
- I'm sorry you
got stuck with me.
很抱歉你被我困住了。
Consider yourself free, okay?
就当你自
- Caleb!
由了，
- ♪ Find me no find ♪
好吗？凯
♪ Catch me no catch ♪
莱布！“找
♪ Unless he's a
matchless match ♪
不到我”“找不到我”“抓不
♪♪
到我”“除非他是无与伦
- ♪
比的比赛”“”
- ESTHA: You need to leave.
你得离开。
- Oh, it's good to
see you too, you fuck!
- 我也很高兴见到你，混蛋! 打
Open the window.
- I can't talk right now.
开窗户-我现在不方便说话。
- Open the window, or I'll
scream my fucking face off.
- 打开窗户，否则我他妈的会大叫的。
You're alive. That's cool.
你还活着，太酷了。
Um, where the hell
have you been?
- 你到底去哪儿了?-
Didn't return any
of my calls, and...
没回我电话..。
I told you I was gonna
be there no matter what.
我告诉过你无论如何我都会去的。
Negative, positive,
I don't care.
消极的，积极的，我不在乎。
- You should leave.
你该走了。
- What? I'll be quiet.
- 什么?-我会安静的。
Your parents, they won't
even know I'm here.
你的父母，他们甚至不会知道我在这里。
- Caleb?
- Okay, I don't care
if you're positive.
-好吧我不管你是否确定。
- I'm not positive.
我不确定。
- You're not positive?
你不确定？真他妈是个
That's fucking amazing news!
好消息！你不确
You're not positive?
定？我们要
We gotta go party!
We gotta get fucking wasted!
去派对了！我们得喝个烂醉！Cale
- Caleb, you should go.
b 你该走了。
- What's going on?
怎么回事？
- Listen.
听着。
You've been a good
friend to me this summer.
这个夏天你一直是我的好朋友。
- Good friend?
- 好朋友
- But, uh, now I have to
focus on the fall and school,
?-但是现在我得专注于秋天和学校,
and, uh, this thing will
have to be behind me.
这件事必须在我身后解决。
- This thing?
这东西？
This thing?
So, wait, you didn't
try to kill yourself?
那么，等等，你不是想自杀?
You're just, like--you're
just, like, ignoring me.
你只是，只是，只是，无视我。
Why is that so much worse?
为什么情况会如此糟糕？
Is it 'cause you're fine?
是因为你没事吗?
And maybe I'm not fine?
也许我不好?-
- Caleb.
Caleb。
- I'm just a
distraction for you.
我只是分散你的注意力。
- What?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 什么?-是啊是啊。
Just like a nice
way to pass the time
就像一个打发时间的好方法
until you go to
your perfect college
直到你上完美的大学
with your perfect friends and
your perfect fucking future--
和你那些完美的朋友，还有你那该死的完美未来
- Caleb. Can't stay
in the summer forever.
Caleb 不能永远待在夏天。
I can't, okay? I'm sorry.
我不能，好吗? ，对不起。
- DAD: Estha! What is going on
in there?
- 伊斯塔!
- ESTHA: Just watching a movie!
Go.
里面怎么了?-看电影而已! 快去。
- Oh, and fuck you for
making me like Taylor Swift.
去你的让我喜欢泰勒 · 斯威夫特。
- ♪
- [knocking on door]
[敲门声]
- Hi.
嗨。
So, how are you?
你好吗?
- Good.
-很好。
How's your grandmother?
你奶奶怎么样
- She's still alive.
了?-她还活着。
Yeah, you could call her.
你可以给她打电话。
- Yeah, I've been busy.
是啊我最近很忙。
With, um...
还有..。
Beth El's Sisterhood.
贝丝 · 艾尔的姐妹情谊。
[unintelligible]
你要喝点什么吗?
You want something to drink?
-好的
- Yes, please.
，谢谢。
- You used to like those.
你以前很喜欢的。
- Hey, where's Aaron?
- EDITH: He's working late.
- 艾伦呢-他加班呢。
You look terrible.
你看起来糟透了。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
- Want me to give
you a ride back home?
- 要我送你回家吗?
I mean, sorry, to
your grandmother's?
不好意思，
- The house is different.
去你奶奶家?-这房子不一样。
- I did some redecorating.
我重新装修了一下。
- It's very cool.
- 这很酷。
Where'd you put his stuff?
你把他的东西放哪儿了？
Can I have this?
- 我能要这
- Yeah, sure.
个吗?-当然。
I ride his bike.
我骑他的自行车。
- I know.
我知道。
Come on, it's time to go.
快点，该走了。
- [baby crying]
[婴儿哭声]
- Hey, it's okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
没事的嘘嘘嘘嘘。
It's okay.
没关系。
It's okay, Seth. It's okay.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
没事的 Seth 没事的嘘嘘嘘。
- Can I hold him?
- 我能抱抱他吗?-
I'll be careful, I promise.
我会小心的我保证。
Please?
求你了？
请坐好吗
- All right, sit down.
Sit down first.
?-好吧，先坐下。
Be careful.
小心点。
You have to hold his head.
你得扶着他的头。
You got him?
- CALEB: Mm-hmm.
你抓住他了?-嗯。
- EDITH: Think he likes you.
我想他喜欢你。
- Hey, little guy.
嘿，小家伙。
Your fingers look
like baby shrimp.
你的手指看起来像小虾。
Definitely not kosher.
肯定不符合犹太教规。
Hey, Mom?
嘿妈妈？
I'm not doing good.
我情况不好。
- No, you're doing fine.
He's not fussing.
不，你做得很好，他没有大惊小怪。
- No, like, I'm...not
doing very good.
不，我... 不是很好。
- What do you mean?
- 什么
What's wrong?
意思? 怎
- Okay, so...I got dumped,
么了?-好吧我被甩了,
and I've been working
really hard at school...
我在学校学习很努力。
- I know.
- CALEB: And...
- 我知道-然后..。
I did something stupid because
I've been sad.
我做了件蠢事，因为我一直很伤心。
He was a complete stranger,
and I kinda liked that.
他是一个完全陌生的人，我有点喜欢这样。
Like, I kinda--
我有点喜
I liked that he didn't know me,
and I was really, really drunk.
欢他不认识我，而且我真的喝醉了。
And I guess the condom
was old or something.
我猜那个避孕套是旧的还是什么的。
- [baby crying]
把他给我。
- EDITH: Give him to me.
- No, Mom.
不，妈妈。
Please.
求你了。
- You need to go.
You need to go now.
你得走了现在就走。
- ♪
- Mom, please,
don't make me leave.
妈妈求你了别让我走。
- [horn blaring]
- [喇叭
- [bells ringing]
声]-[铃声]
- CALEB: Fuck!
- 操!
Fucking, fucking,
fucking, fucking, fuck!
操，操，操，操，操！
- [bridge creaking]
[桥的吱吱声]
- Are you okay?
你还好吗？
- Caleb?
Caleb
Oh, god.
? 天啊。
What happened?
发生什么事了?-
- Everyone leaves me.
每个人都离开了我。
- That's not true.
- CALEB: It is.
- 不是这样的-就是这样。
Dom, Estha, Dad, her.
多姆，伊斯塔，爸爸，她。
Everyone.
每个人。
- I don't know what an Estha is,
我不知道什么是 Estha,
but your dad did not
want to leave you, Caleb.
但你爸爸不想离开你 Caleb。
- That's only
'cause he didn't know
那是因为他不认识
this version of me, the one
with the fucked-up blood.
这个版本的我，那个血迹斑斑的我。
- Oh, your father
would've gone to war for you.
你父亲会为你去打仗的。
He always knew
exactly what you were,
他一直很清楚你是什么人,
and he loved you for it.
他因此爱上了你。
Oh, I hate myself for not
reminding you of that
我恨自己没有每
every single day,
天提醒你,
and it's just so hard
for me to talk about him.
对我来说，谈论他真的很难。
- CALEB: Yeah, and I don't want
to make things harder for you.
- 是啊，我不想让你难做。
I'm not gonna hold you back.
我不会阻止你的。
- You're not holding me back.
- I am.
- 你没有拖我后腿-我有。
From selling the
house, from moving.
从卖房子到搬家。
- Oh, listen, I don't wanna
sell this house because...
听着我不想卖这房子因为..。
your father had his first
haircut in that bathroom.
你父亲第一次理发是在浴室里。
He learned to play the
guitar in that chair.
他在那把椅子上学会了弹吉他。
And I just don't know
how to let him go.
我只是不知道如何让他离开。
It's got nothing to do with you.
这跟你没关系。
You're gonna have
a wonderful life,
你会有一个美好的生活,
no matter what that test says,
不管测试结果如何,
and I can't wait to see it.
我等不及要看了。
- Yeah, how do you know?
- 是啊你怎么知
- I have lived through
two husbands, seven wars...
道?-我经历过两任丈夫七次战争..。
and five revivals of "Oklahoma!"
- [laughs]
还有五部《俄克拉荷马》的复
- I've seen it all.
制片我都看过了。
And, baby, you are
one in a billion.
宝贝，你是十亿分之一。
You're my grandson.
你是我的孙子。
You got my blood in you too,
and don't you ever forget it.
你也有我的血，永远不要忘记。
For that reason alone,
you will do great things.
仅仅因为这个原因，你就会做出伟大的事情。
You will find great love.
你会找到伟大的爱。
And if you're anything like me,
you'll find it more than once.
如果你和我一样，你会发现它不止一次。
- When?
- 什么时候?-
I'm so tired of waiting.
我不想再等了。
- VALERIE: I know, honey, but...
我知道，亲爱的，但是..。
waiting doesn't
mean you shut down.
等待并不意味着你会放弃。
It doesn't mean you turn
yourself into the kind of person
这并不意味着你要把自己
that lets the world
decide who you are
变成那种让世界来决定你
and what you can do.
是谁，你能做什么的人。
You fight for what you want.
你为你想要的而奋斗。
You fight for what you deserve.
你为你应得的而战斗。
I mean, you wait,
我是说你等着,
but you wait with you
fucking fist in the air.
但是你他妈的挥着拳头等着。
That's my boy.
这才是我儿子。
- ♪
- MALE SINGER: ♪ Could've
broken me like glass ♪
本来可以像玻璃一样
♪ In an emergency ♪
打碎我在紧急情况下
♪ It's a giving in ♪
它是个给予我在哪里
♪ Where do I ♪
我不确
- I'm not really
sure how I'm feeling,
定我的感觉如何,
and I think that's okay.
我觉得没关系。
Um, at this point, I'm
just, like, ready to know
在这一点上，我只是，好像，
and move on with my life.
准备知道，并继续我的生活。
- PEDRO: And I knew that I
was gonna be in love in him,
我知道我会爱上他,
that I was gonna fall
in love with him.
我会爱上他。
It is a lot easier for
me to face my own fears
知道他在那里，
and face the uncertainty
of my own life
我更容易面对自己的恐惧
knowing that he's there.
和生活的不确定性。
So I love you.
所以我爱你。
- ♪ Don't try to save me ♪
别想救我
♪ One thing I am sure of ♪
有一件事我很确定
♪ Is everything will change ♪
一切都会改变吗
♪ Time moves us, you grow old ♪
时间推动着我们，你变老了
♪ Days will get rearranged ♪
天会被重新安排
♪ Changing tides ♪
变换潮汐
- Hey, sorry, um...
抱歉。
I know things are
kind of weird, but...
我知道事情有点奇怪但是..。
Can I see you?
我能见你吗？
- ♪ One thing I am sure of ♪
有一件事我很确定
♪ For you, I wait ♪
为了你，我等待着
- [knocking on door]
[敲门声]
- DAD: Estha! You're going
to miss your flight. Let's go!
- 爸爸: Estha! 你要错过你的航班了，我们走！
- ♪ One thing I am sure of ♪
有一件事我很确定
♪ For you, I wait ♪
为了你，我等待着
- DARA: All we ever
talked about
- 达拉: 我们所谈论的
was getting out
of this shithole!
就是离开这鬼地方！
Kinda surprised you
asked to meet me here.
我有点惊讶你会约我在这里见面。
- Well, it's so much more
tolerable when nobody's around.
没人在的时候还能忍受。
I got you something.
我给你带了点东西。
- Is this quiche?
- 这是乳蛋饼吗?
- I hope so.
-希望是。
Is it good?
好吃吗?
- No!
-不好吃！
- Dara.
达拉。
I'm really fucking sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
You're my best friend
and I fucked up.
你是我最好的朋友，我搞砸了。
- I'm really sorry, too.
我也很抱歉。
I quit right after it happened.
事情一发生我就辞职了。
- Good for you.
好样的。
- She had a loose pussy, anyway.
反正她的阴道很松。
- Thank you for that.
谢谢你。
- I finally got a line cook job!
- That's amazing!
- 我终于找到了一份在线厨师的
- At Applebee's.
- Less amazing.
工作!-太棒了!-在苹果蜂餐厅。
But you gotta start somewhere.
- I guess.
但你总得有个开始-我想是吧。
- I leave for New York
in, like, like a week.
我大概一周后就要去纽约了。
- Have you packed already?
- 你已经收拾好了
- CALEB: Do I really need
to answer that question?
吗?-迦勒: 我真的需要回答这个问题吗？
So I get my final
results tomorrow,
我明天就能拿到最终结果了,
and I wanted to see if
you wanna come with?
- 我想问问你要不要一起来
- Yeah, sure, um.
?-好啊当然。
I'll roll some Js for the road.
我会在路上卷一些 j。
- I don't know how you always
know what to say. It's crazy.
我不知道你怎么总是知道该说什么，这太疯狂了。
- ♪
- 你不会让
- You're not gonna
make me eat one.
我吃一个吧。
Gross!
真恶心!
How did I create that?
我是
- [Dara laughing]
怎么创造出来的
- So, I scheduled a
walk-through at that condo
我安排了去好莱坞海滩
on Hollywood Beach, the Orion.
的猎户座公寓看看。
Now, before you
get all cute on me,
在你对我装可爱之前,
I have certain conditions.
我有一定的条件。
- Naturally.
- I live above the 10th floor.
- 当然-我住在10楼以上。
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
- I will have
an oceanfront view.
我会有一个海滨景观。
- DARA: Mm!
- Oh!
- 嗯!-哦!-而且我
- And I will not eat in that
deli more than once a week.
一周不会在那家熟食店吃超过一次的东西。
- Done.
- DARA: Do you think
- 成交-
the resident discount
is transferable?
你认为居民折扣可转让吗?
Not transferable.
不可转让。
- Orion! Wow.
猎户座。
- How you feeling
about tomorrow?
- 你觉得明天怎么样?-尽量
- Try not to think about it.
别去想它。
- You're doing well
'cause you do a lot of things,
你做得很好因为你做了很多事,
but you don't think about it.
- [laughing]
但是你没有想过。-什么? 他很有
What? He's funny!
- Not that funny.
趣!-没那么有趣。
- DARA: He's jealous,
'cause you're not funny.
- 达拉: 他嫉妒,’因为你不有趣。
- ♪
- [everyone laughing]
大家都笑了
- [David Bowie
singing "Five Years"]
- [大卫 · 鲍伊演唱《五年》]
♪ Pushing through
the market square ♪
“推开市场广场”
♪ So many mothers sighing ♪
那么多的母亲在叹息
♪ You said, just come over ♪
你说，过来吧
♪ We had five
years left crying ♪
我们还有五年的时间哭泣
♪ I heard telephones, opera
house, favorite melodies ♪
我听到电话，歌剧院，最喜欢的旋律
♪ I saw boys, toys,
electric irons and TVs ♪
我看到了男孩，玩具，电熨斗和电视
♪ My brain hurt
like a warehouse ♪
我的大脑像仓库一样疼痛
♪ It had no room to spare ♪
它没有多余的空间
♪ I had to cram so many things
to store everything in there ♪
我得塞满这么多东西才能把所有东西都存进去
♪ And all the fat,
skinny people ♪
和所有的胖子，瘦子
♪ And all the tall,
short people ♪
和所有的高个子和矮个子
♪ And all the nobody people ♪
和所有的无名小卒
♪ And all the somebody people ♪
和所有的大人物
♪ I never thought I'd
need so many people ♪
我从没想过我会需要这么多人
♪
♪ I think I saw you in
an ice-cream parlor ♪
我想我在冰淇淋店见过你
♪ Drinking milkshakes
cold and long ♪
喝着冰凉的奶昔
♪ Smiling and waving
and looking so fine ♪
♪微笑着挥手，看起来那么美丽
♪ Don't think you knew
you were in this song ♪
别以为你知道你在这首歌里
♪ And it was cold
and it rained ♪
∮天气很冷，下着雨∮
♪ So I felt like an actor ♪
于是我觉得自己像个演员
♪ And I thought of Ma, and I
wanted to get back there ♪
我想到了妈，我想回到那里
♪ Your face, your race ♪
你的脸，你的种族
- Cohn, Caleb?
科恩，卡莱布？
- ♪ The way that you talk ♪
你说话的方式
♪ I kiss you, you're beautiful,
I want you to walk ♪
我吻你，你很美丽，我要你走路
♪ We've got five years ♪
我们有五年时间
♪ Stuck on my eyes ♪
卡在我的眼睛上
♪ Five years, what a surprise ♪
五年了，多么惊奇啊
♪ We've got five years ♪
我们有五年时间
♪ My brain hurts a lot ♪
我的脑子很疼
♪ Five years,
that's all we got ♪
五年，我们只有这么多了
♪ We've got five years ♪
我们有五年时间
- CALEB: Oh, um, I saw
a flier at the center
- 迦勒: 哦，嗯，我在中心看到一张传单
for a lesbian craft
night tonight. You wanna...
今晚有个拉拉手工之夜你想..。
You wanna go?
你想去吗?-好的，
- Okay, but there
won't be boys there.
但那里不会有男孩。
- Yeah, from this
moment, truly a blessing.
从现在开始真的是上帝的恩赐。
- Um, sure, yeah.
当然可以。
But only if you really feel up
to it. No pressure.
但是只有你真的觉得可以的时候，不要有压力。
- No, I know, we can finally
bag you a single lady.
我知道我们终于可以给你找个单身女人了。
I heard the craft night is
packed with eligible bottoms.
我听说工艺之夜挤满了合格的底裤。
- Aren't I a bottom?
- 我不是垫底
- You're a top.
吗?-你是垫底。
Yeah.
是的。
- ♪
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
♪ What a surprise ♪
♪真是个惊喜♪
♪ We've got five years ♪
我们有五年时间
♪ Stuck on my eyes ♪
卡在我的眼睛上
♪ We've got five years ♪
我们有五年时间
♪ My brain hurts a lot ♪
我的脑子很疼
♪ Five years, that's
all we've got ♪
五年，我们只有这么多了
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
♪
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
♪
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
♪
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
♪
♪ Five years ♪
♪五年♪
- MALE SINGER: ♪ Could've
broken me like glass ♪
可以像打碎玻璃一样打碎我
♪ In an emergency ♪
在紧急情况下
♪ It's like giving in ♪
就像是放弃一样
♪ Where do I begin ♪
我从哪里开始
♪ Bless the skies,
I don't know why ♪
歌颂天空，我不知为什么
♪ I hate Florida sometimes ♪
我有时讨厌佛罗里达
♪ Is it take and take ♪
是拿走还是拿走
♪ Is it my mistake ♪
是我的错吗
♪ What I used to
know, I don't know ♪
我曾经知道的，我不知道
♪ Just spin me,
I'll lose control ♪
让我旋转，我会失去控制
♪ Well, it feels
like I'm on my own ♪
好吧，感觉就像我是一个人
♪ Don't try to save me ♪
别想救我
♪ One thing I am sure of ♪
有一件事我很确定
♪ Is everything will change ♪
一切都会改变吗
♪ Time moves us, you grow old ♪
时间推动着我们，你变老了
♪ Days will get rearranged ♪
天会被重新安排
♪ Changing tides, I
feel it in my bones ♪
变换潮汐，我感觉它在我的骨头里
♪ And I don't ask why
and I just let them go ♪
我不问为什么，我只是让他们离开
♪ 'Cause I know one
thing I am sure of ♪
因为我知道一件事，我确定
♪ For you, I wait ♪
为了你，我等待着
♪
♪ You are sad, you
dig your heels ♪
你很悲伤，你挖你的脚跟
♪ On who I am and
what is real ♪
我是谁，什么是真实的
♪ Only you and me ♪
只有你和我
♪ And all we're going to be ♪
我们将要成为
♪ What I used to
know, I don't know ♪
我曾经知道的，我不知道
♪ Just spin me,
I'll lose control ♪
让我旋转，我会失去控制
♪ But it feels like
I'm on my own ♪
但是感觉就像是我独自一人
♪ Don't try to save me ♪
别想救我
♪ One thing I am sure of ♪
有一件事我很确定
♪ Is everything will change ♪
一切都会改变吗
- ♪
- MALE SINGER: ♪
Accidental lover ♪
偶然的爱人
♪ What'd you do with
all my common sense ♪
你对我的常识做了什么
♪
♪ You came in undercover ♪
你进来卧底
♪ When I didn't
even want a friend ♪
当我甚至不需要朋友的时候
♪
♪ I'm tired of living
like I'm dying ♪
我厌倦了像快死一样的生活
♪ And now I can find a
silver lining like before ♪
现在我能找到一线希望就像以前一样
♪ Yeah, like before ♪
是的，就像以前一样
♪ You got a funny
sense of timing ♪
你对时间的把握很有意思
♪ Showed up on the night
that I start trying ♪
在我开始尝试的那个夜晚出现
♪ For something more ♪
为了更多的东西
♪ And I'm like, oh, sweet,
gotta think I'm in trouble ♪
我就像，哦，亲爱的，我觉得我有麻烦了
♪ Kinda making me wonder ♪
有点让我好奇
♪ What it's like
on the other side ♪
在另一边是什么样的
♪ And I'm like, baby, you're
kinda driving me crazy ♪
我就像，宝贝，你快把我逼疯了
♪ I'm not one to need saving ♪
我不是一个需要拯救的人
♪ But I guess I'll
give it a try ♪
但我想我会试试看
- FEMALE SINGER: ♪ Oh my oh my ♪
哦，我的天，我的天
♪ Down, down, lover ♪
下来，下来，爱人
♪ What I tell you
is in confidence ♪
我告诉你的都是保密的
♪ Laying here together
makes me want to take ♪
♪躺在这里让我
♪ A second chance ♪
想要拿下♪
- ♪
一个第二次机会